<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Processed Benzinga News Feed</title>
<link>http://marketspectator.com/</link>
<description>Processed Benzinga News Feed</description>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:30:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
<language>en-us</language>
<item>
<title>U.S. Patent For 3D Movement Data Goes To Red Light Holland Subsidiary, More AI Innovation Ahead</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35355604/u-s-patent-for-3d-movement-data-goes-to-red-light-holland-subsidiary-more-ai-innovation-ahead</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35355604/u-s-patent-for-3d-movement-data-goes-to-red-light-holland-subsidiary-more-ai-innovation-ahead</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:25:44 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Canadian mushrooms producer <strong>Red Light Holland&rsquo;s</strong> (OTCQB:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TRUFF#OTCQB">TRUFF</a>) wholly-owned tech subsidiary <strong>Radix Motion</strong> received a U.S. patent grant for the <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/22/12/29995855/psychedelic-therapy-boosted-by-3d-movement-data-this-company-is-aiming-to-patent-the-combination">use of human movement data</a> in psychedelic-assisted therapy (PAT).</p>

<p>Attained through the USPTO&rsquo;s Patent Prosecution Highway (PTT) program&nbsp;with an issuing date of&nbsp;Nov. 7, Radix Motion&#39;s claims include using such data as a tool to promote positive experiences, to prevent negative experiences, to predict and personalize individual patient experiences, and to evaluate the therapy&rsquo;s efficacy.</p>

<p>The Silicon Valley-based company aims to file a continuation application to keep the application family open in order to seek additional allowed claims and new patents. This includes using the technology in real-time analysis to identify the position and body movement of a psychedelic facilitator or therapist to detect potential violations and consequently activate real-time alerts and safety measures.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Importantly, Radix Motion asserts that its technology does not require sending or storing any video information, and &ldquo;helps to protect patient privacy.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>CEO Sarah Hashkes</strong> says that as medical and wellness access to PAT grows, so does the need for technology potentially helping with data-driven decisions and real-time protection of patients and clients.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&quot;Human movement data in combination with AI is also an untapped area, which we believe should be included, for clinical research and new psychedelic compound development,&quot; Hashkes added.</p>

<p><strong>Patent attorney</strong> and Red Light Holland&rsquo;s senior advisor <strong>Graham Pechenik</strong> said the team moved through patent prosecution &ldquo;in record time,&rdquo; partly thanks to the received so-called first action allowance, and showing the technology&rsquo;s &ldquo;real uniqueness.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>RLH&rsquo;s CEO and director Todd Shapiro</strong> echoed the sentiment.&nbsp;&ldquo;I&rsquo;m proud that our embodied technology can help establish responsible best practices around psychedelics and contribute to positive change in the emerging psychedelic ecosystem.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Shapiro says the patent is an important milestone, further viewing its potential licensing or sale as another revenue stream for Red Light Holland.</p>

<p>Through its focus on building immersive and embodied technology for health and wellness, Radix Motion&rsquo;s other products include Meu, an AR/VR interactive hologram messenger,&nbsp;iMicroapp, a microdosing app also measuring poses&nbsp;and Wisdom VR, an interactive education on psychedelics.</p>

<p><em>Photo: Benzinga edit with photo by&nbsp;Photon photo and Jynto on Wikimedia Commons.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cannabis Based Pain Relief Solution Receives European Patent Approval</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35348597/cannabis-based-pain-relief-solution-receives-european-patent-approval</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35348597/cannabis-based-pain-relief-solution-receives-european-patent-approval</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:18:41 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>IGC Pharma, Inc</strong>. (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/IGC#NYSE">IGC</a>) <strong>has been granted European Patent No. 3193862 by the European Patent Office </strong>for its innovative &quot;Cannabinoid Composition and Method for Treating Pain.&quot;</p>

<p>The newly granted patent introduces a pioneering method for treating pain in humans.</p>

<h3>How It Works</h3>

<p>Utilizing a cream base infused with a unique blend of cannabinoids, including<strong> </strong>tetrahydrocannabinol (THC) and cannabidiol (CBD) as well as&nbsp;other compounds, the cream or gel is designed for transdermal absorption.</p>

<p>It interacts harmoniously with the peripheral nervous and immune systems, effectively relieving pain without psychotropic or adverse side effects.</p>

<p>Recent consumer trends indicate a profound demand for safe and effective pain relief, and IGC Pharma is seeking to advance pain relief therapies, said<strong> Ram Mukunda, </strong>the company&#39;s CEO.</p>

<p>&quot;We aspire to redefine the standard for pain management, providing healthier alternatives to traditional medications,&quot; Makunda continued.</p>

<p><em>Read also: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/01/30318542/cannabis-effective-for-chronic-pain-substituting-opioids-johns-hopkins-univ-of-michigan-study-co">Cannabis Effective For Chronic Pain, Substituting Opioids: Johns Hopkins &amp; Univ. Of Michigan Study Confirms</a></em></p>

<h3>Alternative Solution For Pain Management</h3>

<p>In America alone, over 56 million individuals grapple with debilitating arthritis, while 10 to&nbsp;30% of total joint arthroplasty patients endure persistent pain. Health economists estimated the annual cost of pain management in the U.S.&nbsp;ranged&nbsp;from $560 billion to $635 billion in 2012, the company said, citing the Journal of Pain&#39;s data.</p>

<p>&quot;Our portfolio now boasts an impressive 35 patent filings in various countries, including the U.S. and Canada,&quot; Makunda said. &quot;I believe that our innovative approach to pain relief has the potential to disrupt the industry, providing investors with a unique chance to be part of a transformative journey. With a substantial addressable market and a strong intellectual property portfolio, we are well-positioned for growth.&quot;</p>

<p><em>Now read:<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/03/31509368/after-17-years-of-side-effects-from-standard-drugs-chronic-pain-patient-finds-relief-with-cannab"> After 17 Years Of Side Effects From Standard Drugs, Chronic Pain Patient Finds Relief With Cannabis: Study</a></em></p>

<p><em><strong>Missed the first wave of cannabis investments? Don&rsquo;t make that mistake again.</strong><br />
Experts believe <strong><a class="c-link" href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">cannabis stocks have found their floor</a></strong><strong> and are now poised for unprecedented growth.</strong> Join <strong><a class="c-link" href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Benzinga PotProfits</a></strong><strong>. </strong>Benefit from <a class="c-link" href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Michael Berger&rsquo;s sharp analysis</a>, revealing top cannabis stock opportunities and timely updates. Experience the potential of 10%+ returns in just 90 days. Our 4.5-star Marketfy rating speaks volumes. Secure your position in this booming sector with a <strong>30-day money-back guarantee.</strong> The time to invest is now, before everyone else realizes it. Secure your profits with Benzinga. <a class="c-link" href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Click here now to learn more</a>.</em></p>

<h3>IGC Price Action</h3>

<p>IGC&rsquo;s <strong>shares traded 6.66% lower at $0.3001 per share </strong>during the pre-market session on Friday morning</p>

<p><em>Photo: Courtesy of <a href="https://unsplash.com/@towfiqu999999?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Towfiqu barbhuiya</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/person-holding-hands-of-another-person-3AsiVDsZnHg?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Court Slaps Trump With $5,000 Penalty Over Disparaging Website Post</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358877/court-slaps-trump-with-5-000-penalty-over-disparaging-website-post</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358877/court-slaps-trump-with-5-000-penalty-over-disparaging-website-post</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:03:42 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>On Friday, a judge handed down a $5,000 fine to former President <strong>Donald Trump</strong> over a derogatory post about a court staffer that remained on the website of his campaign for several weeks. The fine comes as part of Trump&#39;s ongoing civil <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35325129/court-employee-gets-arrested-for-disrupting-donald-trumps-new-york-civil-fraud-trial-i-am-just-here">fraud trial in New York.</a></p>

<p><strong>What Happened</strong>: Judge <strong>Arthur Engoron</strong> slapped the fine on Trump for not promptly removing a disparaging post about a court staffer from his campaign website, despite being ordered to do so, the&nbsp;<a href="https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-letitia-james-fraud-contempt-new-york-ce593e3ee07d95bb6ec7e2de23f47dc9">Associated Press</a>&nbsp;reported.</p>

<p>The judge chose not to hold Trump in contempt for now but reserved the right to reconsider, including the possibility of jail time, if further violations occur.</p>

<p><em>See Also: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35327150/trumps-niece-says-ex-president-should-trademark-the-word-loser-as-jim-jordan-fails-to-clinch-house-s?itm_source=parsely-api" target="_blank">Trump&#39;s Niece Says Ex-President Should Trademark The Word &#39;Loser&#39; As Jim Jordan Fails To Clinch House Spe</a></em></p>

<p><strong>Christopher Kise</strong>, Trump&#39;s lawyer, attributed the failure to erase the post to an unintentional oversight by Trump&#39;s sizable campaign team. The post was finally removed late Thursday after Engoron brought it to the attention of Trump&#39;s legal team, according to the AP.</p>

<p>The judge stressed that Trump is ultimately accountable for his campaign&#39;s actions, even if the failure to remove the post was unintentional. He gave Trump 10 days to settle the $5,000 penalty.</p>

<p><strong>Why It Matters</strong>: The fine comes after the former president was issued a gag order by Engoron earlier in the trial.&nbsp;The gag order was in response to <a href="http://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35076883/trump-hit-with-gag-order-in-civil-fraud-trial-judge-says-ex-presidents-remarks-about-his-staff-unacc">Trump&#39;s social media criticisms</a> of the judge&rsquo;s chief law clerk. The judge deemed such remarks unacceptable and warned of serious sanctions for any breaches of the order, potentially including fines or contempt of court charges.</p>

<p><em>Read Next: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35324682/jamie-raskin-says-these-gop-candidates-could-win-democratic-votes-for-speakership?itm_source=parsely-api" target="_blank">Jamie Raskin Says These GOP Candidates Could Win Democratic Votes For Speakership</a></em></p>

<p><em>Photo: Shutterstock.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>What 9 Analyst Ratings Have To Say About SL Green Realty</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35358927/what-9-analyst-ratings-have-to-say-about-sl-green-realty</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35358927/what-9-analyst-ratings-have-to-say-about-sl-green-realty</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:00:48 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Within the last quarter, SL Green Realty (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/SLG#NYSE">SLG</a>) has observed the following analyst ratings: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">4</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">4</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>These 9 analysts have an average price target of $35.33 versus the current price of SL Green Realty at $31.75, implying  upside.</p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 9 analysts rated SL Green Realty over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697835644_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average has increased by 6.26% from the previous average price target of $33.25. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/SLG/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on SL Green Realty analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>Analyst Ratings: What Are They?</h1>
<p>Ratings come from analysts, or specialists within banking and financial systems that report for specific stocks or defined sectors (typically once per quarter for each stock). Analysts usually derive their information from company conference calls and meetings, financial statements, and conversations with important insiders to reach their decisions.</p>
<p>Some analysts also offer predictions for helpful metrics such as earnings, revenue, and growth estimates to provide further guidance as to what to do with certain tickers. It is important to keep in mind that while stock and sector analysts are specialists, they are also human and can only forecast their beliefs to traders.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>What 22 Analyst Ratings Have To Say About Global Payments</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35358918/what-22-analyst-ratings-have-to-say-about-global-payments</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35358918/what-22-analyst-ratings-have-to-say-about-global-payments</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:00:39 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past 3 months, 22 analysts have published their opinion on Global Payments (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/GPN#NYSE">GPN</a>) stock. These analysts are typically employed by large Wall Street banks and tasked with understanding a company's business to predict how a stock will trade over the upcoming year.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">11</td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">8</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>According to 22 analyst offering 12-month price targets in the last 3 months, Global Payments has an average price target of $143.91 with a high of $211.00 and a low of $105.00. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 22 analysts rated Global Payments over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697835636_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This average price target has increased by 5.35% over the past month.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/GPN/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Global Payments analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>Analyst Ratings: What Are They?</h1>
<p>Ratings come from analysts, or specialists within banking and financial systems that report for specific stocks or defined sectors (typically once per quarter for each stock). Analysts usually derive their information from company conference calls and meetings, financial statements, and conversations with important insiders to reach their decisions.</p>
<p>Some analysts publish their predictions for metrics such as growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide additional guidance with their ratings. When using analyst ratings, it is important to keep in mind that stock and sector analysts are also human and are only offering their opinions to investors.</p>
<p>If you want to keep track of which analysts are outperforming others, you can view updated analyst ratings along withanalyst success scores in <a href="https://benzinga.grsm.io/register174">Benzinga Pro</a>.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Analyst Ratings for Associated Banc</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35358908/analyst-ratings-for-associated-banc</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35358908/analyst-ratings-for-associated-banc</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:00:31 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past 3 months, 4 analysts have published their opinion on Associated Banc (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/ASB#NYSE">ASB</a>) stock. These analysts are typically employed by large Wall Street banks and tasked with understanding a company's business to predict how a stock will trade over the upcoming year.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>In the last 3 months, 4 analysts have offered 12-month price targets for Associated Banc. The company has an average price target of $20.25 with a high of $24.00 and a low of $18.00. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 4 analysts rated Associated Banc over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697835627_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This average price target has increased by 5.91% over the past month.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/ASB/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Associated Banc analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>Analyst Ratings: What Are They?</h1>
<p>Ratings come from analysts, or specialists within banking and financial systems that report for specific stocks or defined sectors (typically once per quarter for each stock). Analysts usually derive their information from company conference calls and meetings, financial statements, and conversations with important insiders to reach their decisions.</p>
<p>Some analysts also offer predictions for helpful metrics such as earnings, revenue, and growth estimates to provide further guidance as to what to do with certain tickers. It is important to keep in mind that while stock and sector analysts are specialists, they are also human and can only forecast their beliefs to traders.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Here's How Much You Would Have Made Owning ONEOK Stock In The Last 20 Years</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358906/heres-how-much-you-would-have-made-owning-oneok-stock-in-the-last-20-years</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358906/heres-how-much-you-would-have-made-owning-oneok-stock-in-the-last-20-years</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:00:28 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>ONEOK (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/OKE#NYSE">OKE</a>) has outperformed the market over the past 20 years by 2.75% on an annualized basis producing an average annual return of 9.94%. Currently, ONEOK has a market capitalization of $39.36 billion. </p>
<p><strong>Buying $1000 In OKE:</strong> If an investor had bought $1000 of OKE stock 20 years ago, it would be worth <strong>$6,612.52</strong> today based on a price of $67.58 for OKE at the time of writing.</p>
<h3>ONEOK's Performance Over Last 20 Years</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697835624_0.png" alt="comp_fig" /></p>

<p>Finally -- what's the point of all this? The key insight to take from this article is to note how much of a difference compounded returns can make in your cash growth over a period of time.</p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>What 23 Analyst Ratings Have To Say About Eli Lilly</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35358905/what-23-analyst-ratings-have-to-say-about-eli-lilly</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35358905/what-23-analyst-ratings-have-to-say-about-eli-lilly</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:00:23 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Analysts have provided the following ratings for Eli Lilly (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/LLY#NYSE">LLY</a>) within the last quarter: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">16</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">4</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">9</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>According to 23 analyst offering 12-month price targets in the last 3 months, Eli Lilly has an average price target of $598.61 with a high of $710.00 and a low of $470.00. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 23 analysts rated Eli Lilly over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697835619_0_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average has increased by 16.98% from the previous average price target of $511.71. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/LLY/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Eli Lilly analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>How Are Analyst Ratings Determined?</h1>
<p>Analysts are specialists within banking and financial systems that typically report for specific stocks or within defined sectors. These people research company financial statements, sit in conference calls and meetings, and speak with relevant insiders to determine what are known as analyst ratings for stocks. Typically, analysts will rate each stock once a quarter. </p>
<p>Some analysts publish their predictions for metrics such as growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide additional guidance with their ratings. When using analyst ratings, it is important to keep in mind that stock and sector analysts are also human and are only offering their opinions to investors.</p>
<p>If you want to keep track of which analysts are outperforming others, you can view updated analyst ratings along withanalyst success scores in <a href="https://benzinga.grsm.io/register174">Benzinga Pro</a>.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Here's How Much $1000 Invested In Las Vegas Sands 15 Years Ago Would Be Worth Today</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358904/heres-how-much-1000-invested-in-las-vegas-sands-15-years-ago-would-be-worth-today</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358904/heres-how-much-1000-invested-in-las-vegas-sands-15-years-ago-would-be-worth-today</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:00:23 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Las Vegas Sands (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/LVS#NYSE">LVS</a>) has outperformed the market over the past 15 years by 3.34% on an annualized basis producing an average annual return of 14.69%. Currently, Las Vegas Sands has a market capitalization of $34.64 billion. </p>
<p><strong>Buying $1000 In LVS:</strong> If an investor had bought $1000 of LVS stock 15 years ago, it would be worth <strong>$7,170.89</strong> today based on a price of $45.31 for LVS at the time of writing.</p>
<h3>Las Vegas Sands's Performance Over Last 15 Years</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697835619_0.png" alt="comp_fig" /></p>

<p>Finally -- what's the point of all this? The key insight to take from this article is to note how much of a difference compounded returns can make in your cash growth over a period of time.</p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Latest Analyst Ratings for Union Pacific</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35358898/the-latest-analyst-ratings-for-union-pacific</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35358898/the-latest-analyst-ratings-for-union-pacific</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:00:16 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past 3 months, 27 analysts have published their opinion on Union Pacific (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/UNP#NYSE">UNP</a>) stock. These analysts are typically employed by large Wall Street banks and tasked with understanding a company's business to predict how a stock will trade over the upcoming year.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">8</td>
<td align="right">9</td>
<td align="right">10</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">8</td>
<td align="right">7</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>In the last 3 months, 27 analysts have offered 12-month price targets for Union Pacific. The company has an average price target of $251.78 with a high of $285.00 and a low of $182.00. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 27 analysts rated Union Pacific over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697835613_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This average price target has increased by 9.9% over the past month.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/UNP/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Union Pacific analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>What Are Analyst Ratings?</h1>
<p>Analysts work in banking and financial systems and typically specialize in reporting for stocks or defined sectors. Analysts may attend company conference calls and meetings, research company financial statements, and communicate with insiders to publish "analyst ratings" for stocks. Analysts typically rate each stock once per quarter.</p>
<p>Some analysts publish their predictions for metrics such as growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide additional guidance with their ratings. When using analyst ratings, it is important to keep in mind that stock and sector analysts are also human and are only offering their opinions to investors.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>A Look Into Vertex Pharmaceuticals Inc's Price Over Earnings</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358746/a-look-into-vertex-pharmaceuticals-incs-price-over-earnings</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358746/a-look-into-vertex-pharmaceuticals-incs-price-over-earnings</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:45:39 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In the current market session, <strong>Vertex Pharmaceuticals Inc. (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/VRTX#NASDAQ">VRTX</a>)</strong> stock price is at $361.86, after a <strong>0.81%</strong> decrease. However, over the past month, the company's stock went up by <strong>3.53%</strong>, and in the past year, by <strong>16.54%</strong>. Shareholders might be interested in knowing whether the stock is overvalued, even if the company is not performing up to par in the current session. </p>
<p><p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697834735_0.png" alt="Past Year Chart" /></p></p>
<h3>Evaluating Vertex Pharmaceuticals P/E in Comparison to Its Peers</h3>
<p>The P/E ratio is used by long-term shareholders to assess the company's market performance against aggregate market data, historical earnings, and the industry at large. A lower P/E could indicate that shareholders do not expect the stock to perform better in the future or it could mean that the company is undervalued. </p>
<p>Compared to the aggregate P/E ratio of the <strong>37.07</strong> in the Biotechnology industry, Vertex Pharmaceuticals Inc. has a lower P/E ratio of <strong>28.19</strong>. Shareholders might be inclined to think that  the stock might perform worse than it's industry peers. It's also possible that the stock is undervalued. </p>
<p><p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697834735_1.png" alt="Guage" /></p></p>
<p>In conclusion, the price-to-earnings ratio is a useful metric for analyzing a company's market performance, but it has its limitations. While a lower P/E can indicate that a company is undervalued, it can also suggest that shareholders do not expect future growth. Additionally, the P/E ratio should not be used in isolation, as other factors such as industry trends and business cycles can also impact a company's stock price. Therefore, investors should use the P/E ratio in conjunction with other financial metrics and qualitative analysis to make informed investment decisions. </p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tesla Stock Down After Q3 Earnings, Gene Munster Says 'Dark Chapter' For EV Company Could Last A Year</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/23/10/35357591/tesla-stock-down-after-q3-earnings-gene-munster-says-dark-chapter-for-ev-company-co</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/23/10/35357591/tesla-stock-down-after-q3-earnings-gene-munster-says-dark-chapter-for-ev-company-co</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:36:27 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Investors in electric vehicle company <strong>Tesla Inc </strong>(NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TSLA#NASDAQ">TSLA</a>) saw shares drop on the week after the company <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35318136/tesla-q3-earnings-highlights-revenue-miss-eps-miss-cybertruck-launch-set-for-november-and-more">reported third-quarter financial results </a>that came in below estimates from analysts.</p>

<p>While there are plenty of potential catalysts for Tesla in the future such as&nbsp;FSD, robotaxis, Taxi Bot, more vehicles, and the launch of the Cybertruck, <strong>one Tesla investor sees more short-term pain ahead.</strong></p>

<p><strong>What Happened:</strong> Analysts have been <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/23/10/35332610/tesla-sized-up-by-9-analysts-after-q3-earnings-mini-disaster-conference-call-first-">mixed on Tesla </a>going forward after the company reported third-quarter financial results. A conference call that saw an overall cautious tone from the company and CEO Elon Musk was also among the concerns from analysts and investors.</p>

<p>With short-term concerns, Tesla could have a dark chapter that lasts a year, according to <strong>Deepwater Asset Manager</strong> co-founder and Managing Partner<strong> Gene Munster.&nbsp;</strong></p>

<p><strong>&ldquo;Tesla&rsquo;s September results and outlook commentary revealed a double whammy of pressures on the business, prolonged margin pressure, and dampened demand outlook,&rdquo; Munster <a href="https://deepwatermgmt.com/teslas-dark-chapter-will-likely-last-a-year-then-things-brighten/">said</a>.</strong></p>

<p>Munster said the next year could be the most difficult period of time for Tesla since the ramp-up of the Tesla Model 3 in 2019.</p>

<p>One key item from the quarterly report was gross margins, which were significantly lower than many were expecting.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Gross margins are central to the Tesla investment case because the metric best gauges whether the company is on track to be valued as a tech company or just another automaker.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Munster said the miss by Tesla on gross margins was worse than anticipated.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Even worse, the potential for margin improvement over the next year was essentially taken off the table.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Another item that may have spooked investors was comments from Musk on Tesla&rsquo;s goal of average annual unit growth of 50%.</p>

<p>&ldquo;It&rsquo;s not possible to have a compound growth rate of 50% forever or you will exceed the mass of the known universe,&rdquo; Musk said.</p>

<p><em>Related Link:<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/trading-ideas/long-ideas/23/10/35336037/trading-strategies-for-tesla-stock-post-q3-earnings-miss"> Trading Strategies For Tesla Stock Post Q3 Earnings Miss&nbsp;</a></em></p>

<p><strong>What&rsquo;s Next:</strong> One of the biggest items shared during the third quarter results was the fact that the highly anticipated <strong>Cybertruck will begin deliveries in November for Tesla, later revealed to be a Nov. 30 delivery event.</strong></p>

<p>Musk was cautious about the outlook of the ramp-up for the Cybertruck, but investors and analysts remain bullish on the potential of the catalyst that has been years in the making.</p>

<p>Tesla confirmed that pre-orders for the Cybertruck are over one million, which is a huge number, but could be lower than <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/08/33995360/how-many-cybertruck-reservations-are-there-tesla-fans-predict-a-staggering-total-ahead-of-launch">third-party estimates</a>, which are closer to two million.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Given Cybertruck will take orders away from the F Series, I believe Cybertruck will be the best-selling truck in the U.S. in 2025 or 2026.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The F-Series from <strong>Ford Motor Co</strong>&nbsp;(NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/F#NYSE">F</a>) is currently the bestselling truck in the U.S. annually and<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/01/30337806/tesla-had-a-top-10-selling-vehicle-in-the-us-for-2022-what-it-means-and-whats-next-for-2023"> has been for decades.</a> Munster saw around 500,000 to 750,000 of the Cybertruck pre-orders materializing and Tesla&rsquo;s ramp up getting to around 500,000 Cybertrucks delivered annually and the vehicle also taking market share away from the popular Ford truck.</p>

<p>Another positive takeaway from Munster is the tough place that traditional automakers and Tesla rivals find themselves in today.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Tesla has the upper hand when it comes to building a car company with an electric focus from the ground up. Today, traditional car companies are facing multiple headwinds when it comes to making the shift to electric vehicles.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Munster said traditional carmakers have two options in the future. The car companies can release a vehicle with similar features to Tesla vehicle and sell it at cost, which would be around 10% to 25% higher than the comparable Tesla vehicle. Or, traditional automakers can subsidize the vehicles to try and take away market share from Tesla, which will also result in increased losses.</p>

<p><strong>&ldquo;We believe car companies that have been around for 50+ years will eventually (10 years from now) be forced to restructure or go out of business.&rdquo;</strong></p>

<p>Munster also sees a bright future ahead for Tesla.</p>

<p>&ldquo;I believe the long-term opportunity remains intact: The company has a pole position in what will be a massive market transition to electrification,&rdquo; Munster said.</p>

<p><strong>TSLA Price Action</strong>: Tesla shares traded at $213.03 at the time of writing versus a 52-week trading range of $101.81 to $299.29. Shares are up 97% year-to-date in 2023 and were down around 15% over the last week.</p>

<p><em>Read Next:<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35068972/heres-how-many-vehicles-tesla-has-delivered-produced-in-each-quarter-since-2019"> Here&#39;s How Many Vehicles Tesla Has Delivered &amp; Produced In Each Quarter Since 2019&nbsp;</a></em><br />
&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Highway Holdings Q2 EPS $(0.08) Down From $0.10 YoY, Sales $1.35M Down From $3.04M YoY</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35358538/highway-holdings-q2-eps-0-08-down-from-0-10-yoy-sales-1-35m-down-from-3-04m-yoy</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35358538/highway-holdings-q2-eps-0-08-down-from-0-10-yoy-sales-1-35m-down-from-3-04m-yoy</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:32:10 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Highway Holdings (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/HIHO#NASDAQ">HIHO</a>) reported quarterly losses of $(0.08) per share. This is a 180 percent decrease over earnings of $0.10 per share from the same period last year. The company reported $1.35 million in sales this quarter. This is a 55.64 percent decrease over sales of $3.04 million the same period last year.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Here's How Much $100 Invested In Pioneer Natural Resources 20 Years Ago Would Be Worth Today</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358503/heres-how-much-100-invested-in-pioneer-natural-resources-20-years-ago-would-be-worth-today</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358503/heres-how-much-100-invested-in-pioneer-natural-resources-20-years-ago-would-be-worth-today</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:30:51 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Pioneer Natural Resources (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/PXD#NYSE">PXD</a>) has outperformed the market over the past 20 years by 4.86% on an annualized basis producing an average annual return of 12.05%. Currently, Pioneer Natural Resources has a market capitalization of $58.75 billion. </p>
<p><strong>Buying $100 In PXD:</strong> If an investor had bought $100 of PXD stock 20 years ago, it would be worth <strong>$989.86</strong> today based on a price of $251.99 for PXD at the time of writing.</p>
<h3>Pioneer Natural Resources's Performance Over Last 20 Years</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697833847_0.png" alt="comp_fig" /></p>

<p>Finally -- what's the point of all this? The key insight to take from this article is to note how much of a difference compounded returns can make in your cash growth over a period of time.</p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Price Over Earnings Overview: Sherwin-Williams</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358481/price-over-earnings-overview-sherwin-williams</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358481/price-over-earnings-overview-sherwin-williams</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:30:16 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking into the current session, <strong>Sherwin-Williams Inc. (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/SHW#NYSE">SHW</a>)</strong> shares are trading at $237.70, after a <strong>0.50%</strong> decrease. Over the past month, the stock fell by <strong>6.66%</strong>, but over the past year, it actually increased by <strong>11.84%</strong>. With questionable short-term performance like this, and great long-term performance, long-term shareholders might want to start looking into the company's price-to-earnings ratio. </p>
<p><p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697833812_0.png" alt="Past Year Chart" /></p></p>
<h3>Sherwin-Williams P/E Compared to Competitors</h3>
<p>The P/E ratio is used by long-term shareholders to assess the company's market performance against aggregate market data, historical earnings, and the industry at large. A lower P/E could indicate that shareholders do not expect the stock to perform better in the future or it could mean that the company is undervalued. </p>
<p>Sherwin-Williams has a lower P/E than the aggregate P/E of <strong>34.47</strong> of the Chemicals industry. Ideally, one might believe that the stock might perform worse than its peers, but it's also probable that the stock is undervalued. </p>
<p><p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697833812_1.png" alt="Guage" /></p></p>
<p>In summary, while the price-to-earnings ratio is a valuable tool for investors to evaluate a company's market performance, it should be used with caution. A low P/E ratio can be an indication of undervaluation, but it can also suggest weak growth prospects or financial instability. Moreover, the P/E ratio is just one of many metrics that investors should consider when making investment decisions, and it should be evaluated alongside other financial ratios, industry trends, and qualitative factors. By taking a comprehensive approach to analyzing a company's financial health, investors can make well-informed decisions that are more likely to lead to successful outcomes. </p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>If You Invested $1,000 In Netflix Stock At Its IPO, Here's How Much You'd Have Now</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/general/entertainment/23/10/35356785/if-you-invested-1-000-in-netflix-stock-at-its-ipo-heres-how-much-youd-have-now</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/general/entertainment/23/10/35356785/if-you-invested-1-000-in-netflix-stock-at-its-ipo-heres-how-much-youd-have-now</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:29:55 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Streaming giant <strong>Netflix Inc</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/NFLX#NASDAQ">NFLX</a>) has been around for 25 years and is a market leader in&nbsp;the streaming sector around the world. Here&rsquo;s a look back at the company&rsquo;s history and how an investment in its IPO<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/18/05/11764543/this-day-in-market-history-netflix-goes-public"> would have fared.</a></p>

<p><strong>What Happened:</strong> Netflix ended the<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35317946/netflix-stock-soars-following-q3-results-eps-beat-revenue-beat-strong-subscriber-growth"> third quarter with </a>247.15 million paid&nbsp;global subscribers, adding 8.8 million paid subscribers in the quarter.&nbsp;</p>

<p>A quarterly report showcasing Netflix&#39;s revenue and earnings per share surpassing analyst predictions has driven the streaming giant&#39;s share price upwards.</p>

<p>The company was <a href="https://www.netflix.com/tudum/articles/netflix-trivia-25th-anniversary">founded </a>in 1997 and launched its website NetfFlix.com on April 14, 1998. Originally known as a DVD-by-mail rental service, Netflix found itself in competition with <strong>Blockbuster </strong>and other physical movie rental chains.</p>

<p>Blockbuster also launched its own DVD-by-mail rental service. A battle between Netflix and Blockbuster raged on for years, before Blockbuster eventually <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/company-news/10/08/445627/bye-bye-blockbuster-video-store-chain-to-file-bankruptcy-next-mont">filed for bankruptcy </a>in 2010 due to its high level of debt.</p>

<p>Back in 2000, Netflix <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/entertainment/23/04/31801202/when-netflix-founders-tried-selling-the-company-to-amazon-blockbuster-they-laughed-us-out-o">pitched a deal</a> to be acquired by Blockbuster for $50 million. The pitch came as Netflix was among the companies feeling the effect of the dot-com market crash. Blockbuster executives are said to have laughed Netflix out of the room.</p>

<p>Before they pitched the company to Blockbuster for an acquisition, Netflix took a meeting with <strong>Amazon.com Inc</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/AMZN#NASDAQ">AMZN</a>) back in 1998. Amazon founder <strong>Jeff Bezos </strong>offered $15 million to acquire Netflix, but the company turned the deal down, believing they had more growth ahead.</p>

<p>The co-founders of Netflix who turned down the Amazon deal are likely happy they did, as are any investors who got in on the streaming company early.</p>

<p>Netflix held its IPO on May 29, 2002, offering 5.5 million shares at a price of $15. Shares posted triple-digit returns for investors over the first several years.</p>

<p>At the time of its IPO, Netflix had around 600,00 subscribers for its DVD-by-mail rental service. The company&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/entertainment/23/04/31883368/after-25-years-of-incredible-run-netflix-breaks-up-with-dvds-its-not-you-its-streaming">recently ended its DVD-by-mail service.</a></p>

<p>Years later, in 2007, Netflix entered the next phase of growth <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/education/23/09/34988686/if-you-invested-1-000-in-netflix-stock-when-company-announced-streaming-launch-heres-how-much-y">by offering streaming</a> to subscribers as part of its existing DVD rental by mail service. Eventually, the company would transition to offering streaming and mail packages separately or as bundles.</p>

<p>In 2012, &ldquo;Lillyhammer&rdquo; became the first original series to hit the Netflix streaming platform. Over the years, Netflix has released plenty of hit shows like &ldquo;House of Cards,&rdquo; &ldquo;Stranger Things,&rdquo; &ldquo;Bridgerton,&rdquo; &quot;Squid Game&quot; and more.</p>

<p><em>Related Link:<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/23/10/35335321/netflix-rallies-off-q3-earnings-8-analysts-on-future-price-increases-ad-supported-p"> Netflix Rallies Off Q3 Earnings, 8 Analysts on Future Price Increases, Ad-Supported Plan&nbsp;</a></em></p>

<p><strong>Investing $1,000 In Netflix Stock:</strong> Although investors couldn&#39;t predict Netflix&#39;s ascendancy as a streaming juggernaut or Blockbuster&#39;s eventual bankruptcy, they might have backed Netflix based on their personal experience as customers or their faith in the company&#39;s innovative vision and consistent growth.</p>

<p>At a price point of $15, an investor could have purchased 66.7 shares at the time of the Netflix IPO. Stock splits in 2004 (2-for-1) and 2015 (7-for-1) would have turned the $1,000 investment into 933.8 shares.</p>

<p>Based on a price of $404.70 for Netflix stock at the time of writing, the $1,000 investment would be worth $377,908.86 today. This represents a return of 37,690.9% for investors.</p>

<p>Netflix shares hit an all-time high of $691.69 on Nov. 17, 2021. The $1,000 investment would have been worth a staggering $645,900.12 at that time.</p>

<p>While past results don&rsquo;t always mean the future will be a success, Netflix remains a market leader in the streaming space and is gaining subscribers with a password-sharing crackdown and ad-supported plan launch.</p>

<p><em>Read Next: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/entertainment/23/09/34832017/heres-when-you-can-watch-netflixs-squid-game-reality-show-and-how-much-the-record-prize-is">Here&#39;s When You Can Watch Netflix&#39;s Squid Game Reality Show And How Much The Record Prize Is&nbsp;</a></em></p>

<p><em>Photo: Shutterstock</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>UAW President Says "We're Striking The Big Three Like We've Never Struck Before"; Ford Dividends Shows "Money Is There" For A Better Offer</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358462/uaw-president-says-were-striking-the-big-three-like-weve-never-struck-before-ford-dividends-shows-mo</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358462/uaw-president-says-were-striking-the-big-three-like-weve-never-struck-before-ford-dividends-shows-mo</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:29:40 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Uaw President Says " Days Of UAW And Ford Being A Team To Fight Other Companies Are Over"; "We Are Going To Organize Non Union Auto Co's Like Never Before"</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358458/uaw-president-says-days-of-uaw-and-ford-being-a-team-to-fight-other-companies-are-over-we-are-going</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358458/uaw-president-says-days-of-uaw-and-ford-being-a-team-to-fight-other-companies-are-over-we-are-going</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:28:30 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>UAW President Says Ford Continues To Stew About Kentucky Truck Plant And Pretend "They Can't Afford What We're Asking For"</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358450/uaw-president-says-ford-continues-to-stew-about-kentucky-truck-plant-and-pretend-they-cant-afford-wh</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358450/uaw-president-says-ford-continues-to-stew-about-kentucky-truck-plant-and-pretend-they-cant-afford-wh</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:26:35 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>UAW President Says On Proposals From Automakers Says ,"There Is More To Be Won"; "These Extremely Profitable Companies Have More To Give"; "Serious Movement At Stellantis And GM"</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358447/uaw-president-says-on-proposals-from-automakers-says-there-is-more-to-be-won-these-extremely-profita</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358447/uaw-president-says-on-proposals-from-automakers-says-there-is-more-to-be-won-these-extremely-profita</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:26:10 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>=</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Worst FIFA Glitch Ever? Trickster+ Bug Plagues EA Sports FC 24  Gamers Are Not Happy</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/general/gaming/23/10/35356619/worst-fifa-glitch-ever-trickster-bug-plagues-ea-sports-fc-24-gamers-are-not-happy</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/general/gaming/23/10/35356619/worst-fifa-glitch-ever-trickster-bug-plagues-ea-sports-fc-24-gamers-are-not-happy</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:25:43 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The FIFA gaming community is currently in turmoil due to a crippling glitch referred to as the &quot;Trickster glitch&quot;&nbsp;that has infiltrated<strong> Electronic Arts Inc&#39;</strong>s (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/EA#NASDAQ">EA</a>) EA Sports FC 24&#39;s highest-level <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/gaming/23/10/35247676/fc-tactical-is-eas-new-turn-based-soccer-rpg-game-for-2024">competitive multiplayer mode.</a></p>

<p><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/ea-sports-fc-24-players-horrified-as-worst-ever-glitch-spreads-to-ultimate-team-weekend-league">According</a> to IGN, this glitch allows players with the Trickster+ playstyle to perform a skill move that attaches the ball to the back of their leg, enabling them to effortlessly score goals without any defense being able to prevent it.</p>

<p><em>See Also:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/entertainment/23/02/30913320/gaming-giant-electronic-arts-takes-on-soccer-pays-588-million-for-premier-league-rights">Gaming Giant Electronic Arts Takes On Soccer: Pays $588 Million for Premier League Rights</a></em></p>

<p>FC 24 players initially used this exploit in Ultimate Team&#39;s Division Rivals mode, but it has now infiltrated the Weekend League, the game&#39;s highest-pressure player-versus-player mode.</p>

<p>EA Sports acknowledged the glitch but has only stated it is&nbsp;investigating it.</p>

<p>&quot;We&#39;ve added a new issue to the EASFC Tracker that we&#39;re investigating. The ball can incorrectly stick to a dribbler&#39;s leg as they run in some situations,&quot; the account EA SPORTS FC Direct Communication posted on X (formerly Twitter).</p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p>We&#39;ve added a new issue to the EASFC Tracker that we&#39;re investigating. The ball can incorrectly stick to a dribbler&#39;s leg as they run in some situations.<a href="https://t.co/oKgcIFd9zn">https://t.co/oKgcIFd9zn</a></p>
&mdash; EA SPORTS FC Direct Communication (@EASFCDirect) <a href="https://twitter.com/EASFCDirect/status/1715072825193574599?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 19, 2023</a></blockquote>
<script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>

<p>Despite fans calling for a delay of the Weekend League to maintain competitive integrity, the weekly mode launched as planned. FC 24 players are now demanding EA Sports take punitive action against those who exploited the glitch and block rewards for affected matches.</p>

<p>In addition to this ongoing issue, FC 24&nbsp;also faced controversies related to microtransactions, including a $30 Ultimate Team pack offered for purchase before the game&#39;s official launch.</p>

<p>It&#39;s worth noting FC 24 launch sales in Europe were down compared to FIFA 23, which was a massive hit for EA, though this decline was anticipated following EA&#39;s severed relationship with FIFA.</p>

<p><em>Read Next:<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/gaming/23/10/35332854/european-game-sales-stumble-in-september-2023-ea-sports-fc-24-nba-2k24-mortal-kombat-1">&nbsp;European Game Sales Stumble In September 2023: EA Sports FC 24, NBA 2K24, Mortal Kombat 1</a></em></p>

<p><em>Photo:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.shutterstock.com/es/g/miglagoa">Miguel Lagoa</a>&nbsp;on Shutterstock.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Semtech 13G Filing Shows Steven A Cohen's Point72 Asset Management, L.P. Reported A 7.3% Stake In The Co As Of October 19</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/m-a/23/10/35358385/semtech-13g-filing-shows-steven-a-cohens-point72-asset-management-l-p-reported-a-7-3-stake-in-the-co</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/m-a/23/10/35358385/semtech-13g-filing-shows-steven-a-cohens-point72-asset-management-l-p-reported-a-7-3-stake-in-the-co</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:23:01 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>- SEC Filing</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Brilliant Acquisition Corporation Announces Extension Of Completion Window to November 23, 2023</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/m-a/23/10/35358283/brilliant-acquisition-corporation-announces-extension-of-completion-window-to-november-23-2023</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/m-a/23/10/35358283/brilliant-acquisition-corporation-announces-extension-of-completion-window-to-november-23-2023</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:17:39 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Brilliant Acquisition Corporation ("Brilliant") announced today that it has extended the period of time it will have to consummate its initial business combination by a further one month, or until November 23, 2023. In connection with the extension, Brilliant's Sponsor, Nisun Investment Holding Limited, deposited $32,300 in Brilliant's trust account, representing $0.08 per public ordinary share of Brilliant currently outstanding, as additional interest on the proceeds in the trust account. The extension was approved by Brilliant's shareholders on July 20, 2023. The shareholder approval also permits Brilliant to further extend Brilliant's initial business combination deadline on a monthly basis up to a further one month, or until December 23, 2023, upon deposit of an additional $32,300 in the trust account for each month.</p><p>The purpose of the extension is to permit sufficient time for Brilliant to consummate its previously announced proposed business combination with Nukkleus, Inc. ("Nukkleus"). For a summary of the material terms of the proposed business combination, please see Brilliant's Current Report on Form 8-K filed on June 26, 2023 with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (the "SEC") and Brilliant's Registration Statement on Form S-4 initially filed with the SEC on July 25, 2023 (as amended to date).</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tether To Publish Reserve Data In Real-Time: Report</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356411/tether-to-publish-reserve-data-in-real-time-report</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356411/tether-to-publish-reserve-data-in-real-time-report</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:17:31 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In a move towards greater transparency, <strong>Tether Holdings</strong>, the entity behind the stablecoin <strong>Tether</strong> (CRYPTO: <a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/">USDT</a>), is said to be revising its approach to publishing reserve data reports.</p>

<p>As the crypto community gears up for Benzinga&#39;s <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/go/crypto-conference-article-link">Future of Digital Assets</a> conference on Nov.&nbsp;14, this development from Tether will likely be a discussion topic. The conference aims to address the evolving landscape of digital assets, and&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>Paolo Ardoino</strong>, soon to be the CEO and currently the chief technology officer of Tether, was <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-10-20/tether-s-incoming-ceo-paolo-ardoino-inherits-crypto-s-stablecoin-giant-usdt?leadSource=uverify%20wall">quoted </a>by Bloomberg on Oct. 20, stating the company&#39;s intention to &quot;publish reserve data in real-time in 2024.&quot;</p>

<p>While Tether had&nbsp;yet to officially comment on this, its transparency page indicated&nbsp;that it&nbsp;currently updates its reserve data daily and provides monthly and quarterly reserve reports.</p>

<p>Benzinga has reached out to Ardoino for a comment.</p>

<p>Despite facing market challenges in 2023, Tether&#39;s performance has been noteworthy.</p>

<p><em>Also Read:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35348753/crypto-space-gets-a-boost-with-european-banking-authority-and-esmas-proposed-regulations">Crypto Space Gets A Boost With European Banking Authority And ESMA&#39;s Proposed Regulations</a></em></p>

<p>Data from its second quarter update revealed&nbsp;a 5.7% growth in assets, reaching a staggering $86.5 billion.</p>

<p>The company reported an &quot;operational profit&quot; exceeding $1 billion, marking a 30% uptick from the preceding quarter.</p>

<p>Interestingly, 2023 saw a revival in Tether&#39;s stablecoin lending activities, a significant shift considering it had ceased such loans entirely in December 2022.</p>

<p>Further insights from Tether&#39;s second quarter&nbsp;attestation, conducted by accounting firm BDO, highlighted an $850 million increase in excess reserves, totaling $3.3 billion.</p>

<p>Tether also revealed an indirect exposure of $72 billion to U.S. Treasuries&nbsp;via money market funds and U.S. Treasuries backing its overnight repo.</p>

<p><em>Read Next:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35347190/crypto-mining-titan-bitdeers-2m-share-repurchase-shaping-the-future-of-digital-assets-on-n">Crypto Mining Titan Bitdeer&#39;s $2M Share Repurchase: Shaping the Future of Digital Assets On Nasdaq?</a></em></p>

<p><em>Join Benzinga&#39;s&nbsp;</em><em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/go/Fintech-article-link" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Fintech Deal Day&nbsp;</a></em><em>&amp; Awards on Nov. 13 and&nbsp;</em><em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/go/crypto-conference-article-link" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Future of Digital Assets</a></em><em>&nbsp;on Nov. 14 in New York City to stay updated on trends like AI, regulations, SEC actions and institutional adoption in the crypto space.&nbsp;</em><em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/go/crypto-conference-article-link" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Secure early bird discounted tickets now</a></em><em>!</em></p>

<p><em>Photo: Shutterstock</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>United Auto Workers President Shawn Fain Says Union Has Gotten New Offers In Past 24 Hours From 2 Of 3 Automakers</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358265/united-auto-workers-president-shawn-fain-says-union-has-gotten-new-offers-in-past-24-hours-from-2-of</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358265/united-auto-workers-president-shawn-fain-says-union-has-gotten-new-offers-in-past-24-hours-from-2-of</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:16:32 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>-</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Binance Expands European Influence With New Euro Services Partnership</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356375/binance-expands-european-influence-with-new-euro-services-partnership</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356375/binance-expands-european-influence-with-new-euro-services-partnership</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:16:04 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Amid&nbsp;organizational shifts and regulatory hurdles, <strong>Binance </strong>is <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/09/34900834/binance-attempts-a-belgium-comeback-just-3-months-after-watchdog-halted-services">bolstering its European</a> foothold with a fresh Euro services partnership.</p>

<p><strong>What Happened?</strong></p>

<p>Crypto exchange giant, Binance&nbsp;announced that it has signed agreements with new regulated and authorized fiat partners for EUR payments, deposits, and withdrawals, as reported on its <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/fiat/binance-expands-freedom-of-money-for-european-users-with-new-eur-fiat-partnerships-3923321843149867820">blog post</a>.</p>

<p>The new partnerships offer EUR transactions via Open Banking and SEPA/SEPA Instant, and buying and selling crypto with SEPA/SEPA Instant. Users have already started to shift to the new services.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Being able to easily convert fiat to crypto, and back to fiat again, is a crucial part of advancing the adoption of digital assets globally. Without an easy way to buy or sell crypto, users who are new to the space can find the process of buying or selling crypto unintuitive and intimidating,&rdquo; Binance said in its blog.</p>

<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p>More EUR fiat channels have arrived on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Binance?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Binance</a><br />
<br />
We&rsquo;re proud to announce that we&rsquo;ve entered into agreements with multiple new EUR partners to provide deposit, withdrawal, and payment services, making your experience even more seamless.<br />
<br />
Find out more &#128071;<a href="https://t.co/jKh2QxH3sN">https://t.co/jKh2QxH3sN</a></p>
&mdash; Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1715041951353827722?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 19, 2023</a></blockquote>
<script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>

<p><em>Find out more on Binance and other crypto exchanges. Meet and engage with other transformative&nbsp;</em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/go/crypto-conference-article-link" target="_blank"><em>Digital Asset and Crypto</em></a><em>&nbsp;business leaders and investors at Benzinga&#39;s exclusive event:&nbsp;</em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/go/crypto-conference-article-link" target="_blank"><em>Future of Digital Assets</em></a><em>. Tickets are flying:&nbsp;</em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/go/crypto-conference-article-link" target="_blank"><em>Get yours</em></a><em>!&nbsp;&nbsp;</em></p>

<p>There is no disclosure of the names of the new service providers. However, a Blockworks <a href="https://blockworks.co/news/binance-europe-services-paysafe">report</a>&nbsp;cites&nbsp;a Binance spokesperson who said that the company has onboarded partners including fintech firm, TrueLayer, global payment tech company, Nuvei and several card acquirers.</p>

<p><em>Read Next: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35249366/legally-tangled-binance-unveils-first-likely-choice-for-altcoin-listing">Legally Tangled Binance Unveils First Likely Choice For Altcoin Listing</a></em></p>

<p><strong>Paysafe Distancing And Other Challenges</strong></p>

<p>The move comes on the heels of <strong>Paysafe</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/PSFE#NYSE">PSFE</a>), Binance&rsquo;s earlier Euro banking partner, <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/09/34980611/binances-paysafe-partnership-ends-users-advised-to-convert-eur-balances-to-usdt">ending its relationship&nbsp;with Binance</a> for providing any further operations in September.</p>

<p><em>Also Read: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35309948/binance-shakes-up-its-portfolio-multiple-trading-pair-delistings-new-additions-unveiled">Binance Shakes Up Its Portfolio: Multiple Trading Pair Delistings, New Additions Unveiled</a></em></p>

<p>PaySafe started showing signs of distance in May 2023 when Binance suspended deposits and withdrawals in British pounds until a new banking partner was secured. These signs were reflected as the exchange faced <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35273208/binance-pauses-uk-registrations-due-to-regulatory-changes">legal inquiries from authorities in the U.K</a>., Japan, Italy, Singapore, Netherlands, Canada and Thailand.</p>

<p>Currently, Binance has halted operations in Germany, Netherlands, and Cyprus amid licensing issues. It has also announced plans to reduce its European footprint and focus on lesser-regulated entities. The exchange is currently <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/06/32718798/binance-and-changpeng-zhao-sued-by-the-sec-has-the-empire-just-started-crumbling">surrounded by regulatory challenges, legal actions</a> and some <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/07/33143894/changpeng-zhao-on-departure-of-key-binance-executives-dreamed-up-reasons-by-news-are-compl">executive departures.</a></p>

<p><em>Benzinga&rsquo;s </em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/events/digital-assets/?UTM_source=article" target="_blank"><em>Future of Digital Assets</em></a><em>&nbsp;conference is scheduled in New York on Nov.14. Attend and learn more about exchanges and their fiat partnerships for withdrawals and deposits. The gathering is seen as pivotal for the digital assets&rsquo; community.&nbsp;The event will spotlight the latest trends, innovations,&nbsp;and challenges in the digital asset realm.</em></p>

<p><em>Photo: Unsplash</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ellington Financial And Great Ajax Corp. Announce Mutual Termination Of Merger Agreement; Ellington Financial Agreed To Pay Great Ajax $16M With $5M Payable In Cash And $11M Paid As Consideration For 1,666,666 Shares Of Stock Purchased At $6.60/Share</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/m-a/23/10/35358205/ellington-financial-and-great-ajax-corp-announce-mutual-termination-of-merger-agreement-ellington-fi</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/m-a/23/10/35358205/ellington-financial-and-great-ajax-corp-announce-mutual-termination-of-merger-agreement-ellington-fi</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:15:42 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The termination was approved by both companies' boards of directors after careful consideration of the proposed merger and the progress made towards completing the proposed merger. In addition, Ellington Financial has agreed to pay Great Ajax $16 million of which $5 million is payable in cash and $11 million was paid as consideration for 1,666,666 shares of Great Ajax common stock, which were purchased at a per share price of $6.60. Ellington Financial will now hold approximately 6.1% of Great Ajax's stock. In addition, an affiliate of the external manager of Ellington Financial owned 273,983 shares of Great Ajax common stock as of June 30, 2023. Ellington Financial remains a securitization joint venture partner as well. The two companies intend to continue to work together on mortgage loan opportunities.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>How Is The Market Feeling About Truist Finl?</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/short-sellers/23/10/35358200/how-is-the-market-feeling-about-truist-finl</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/short-sellers/23/10/35358200/how-is-the-market-feeling-about-truist-finl</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:15:26 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Truist Finl's</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TFC#NYSE">TFC</a>) short percent of float has fallen 14.04% since its last report. The company recently reported that it has <strong>12.98 million shares sold short</strong>, which is 0.98% of all regular shares that are available for trading. Based on its trading volume, <strong>it would take traders 1.14 days to cover their short positions on average.</strong></p>
<h3>Why Short Interest Matters</h3>
<p>Short interest is the number of shares that have been sold short but have not yet been covered or closed out. <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/money/how-to-short-a-stock/">Short selling</a> is when a trader sells shares of a company they do not own, with the hope that the price will fall. Traders make money from short selling if the price of the stock falls and they lose if it rises.</p>
<p>Short interest is important to track because it can act as an indicator of market sentiment towards a particular stock. An increase in short interest can signal that investors have become more bearish, while a decrease in short interest can signal they have become more bullish.</p>
<p><strong>See Also:</strong> <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/short-interest"><strong>List of the most shorted stocks</strong></a></p>
<h3>Truist Finl Short Interest Graph (3 Months)</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697832923_0.png" alt="short_fig" /></p>

<p>As you can see from the chart above the percentage of shares that are sold short for Truist Finl has declined since its last report. This does not mean that the stock is going to rise in the near-term but traders should be aware that less shares are being shorted.</p>
<h3>Comparing Truist Finl's Short Interest Against Its Peers</h3>
<p>Peer comparison is a popular technique amongst analysts and investors for gauging how well a company is performing. A company's peer is another company that has similar characteristics to it, such as industry, size, age, and financial structure. You can find a company's peer group by reading its 10-K, proxy filing, or by doing your own similarity analysis.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://pro.benzinga.com/">Benzinga Pro</a>, Truist Finl's peer group average for short interest as a percentage of float is 4.57%, which means the company has <strong>less</strong> short interest than most of its peers.</p>
<p>Did you know that increasing short interest can actually be <strong>bullish</strong> for a stock? <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/money/how-to-make-money-on-a-short-squeeze/"><strong>This post by Benzinga Money explains how you can profit from it.</strong></a></p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and was reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ames National Q3 EPS $0.33 Down From $0.62 YoY</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35358143/ames-national-q3-eps-0-33-down-from-0-62-yoy</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35358143/ames-national-q3-eps-0-33-down-from-0-62-yoy</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:14:08 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Ames National (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/ATLO#NASDAQ">ATLO</a>) reported quarterly earnings of $0.33 per share. This is a 46.77 percent decrease over earnings of $0.62 per share from the same period last year.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Jimmy Kimmel Declares Snoop Dogg's Birthday 'Half-4/20' Celebration: Introduces DoggFather's Day</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35356562/jimmy-kimmel-declares-snoop-doggs-birthday-half-420-celebration-introduces-doggfathers-day</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35356562/jimmy-kimmel-declares-snoop-doggs-birthday-half-420-celebration-introduces-doggfathers-day</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:12:31 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>In honor of <strong>Snoop Dogg&rsquo;</strong>s birthday and his &ldquo;significant contributions to the popularization of marijuana,&rdquo;&nbsp;<strong>Jimmy Kimmel</strong> declared the rapper&#39;s Oct. 20&nbsp;birthday&nbsp;to be &ldquo;DoggFather&rsquo;s Day,&quot; to be celebrated as a&nbsp;&ldquo;new high holiday.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Kimmel and his sidekick&nbsp;<strong>Guillermo Rodriguez</strong>&nbsp;proceeded to present Snoop with a mock proclamation made from an oversized box of rolling papers on Thursday&#39;s &quot;Jimmy Kimmel Live.&quot;</p>

<p>Kimmel noted that &ldquo;Mr. Dogg&rsquo;s birthday falls on the exact midpoint to 4/20&mdash;a coincidence that is totally tripping me out right now.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Kimmel explained that half-birthdays are a&nbsp;big thing in his family.</p>

<p>&quot;We sing Halfy Birthday, we have half a cake&rdquo;&mdash;and on 4/20 last year, &ldquo;I was sitting there thinking, &lsquo;I wonder what the half-birthday of 4/20 is.&#39;&rdquo;</p>

<p><strong>Then He Declared A New Holiday</strong></p>

<p>&quot;Why shouldn&rsquo;t this be a holiday?&nbsp;Mr. Dogg&rsquo;s birthday falls on the exact midpoint to 4/20.&quot;</p>

<p>Then&nbsp;Kimmel read the&nbsp;proclamation:&nbsp;&ldquo;Whereas, <strong>Calvin Cordozar Broadus Jr.</strong>, known worldwide as Snoop Doggy Dogg, has made significant contributions to the popularization of <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/money/marijuana-stocks/">marijuana</a>&mdash;AKA weed, pot, ganja, herb, bud, trees, cheeba, kush, chronic, reefer, dank, sticky icky icky and jolly green giggle sticks.&quot;</p>

<p>&quot;Whereas, Mr. Dogg&rsquo;s birthday miraculously&nbsp;falls on the exact midway point to 4/20&mdash;a coincidence that is totally tripping me out right now,&rdquo; Kimmel added.</p>

<p>The late-night host&nbsp;then encouraged the audience to bow their heads and join him in a chant: &ldquo;Bow-Wow-Wow Yippie-Yo-Yippie-Yay-men.&rdquo; He presented Snoop with what he said was the new &ldquo;Presidential Medal of Weedom.&rdquo;</p>

<p><em>More on Snoop&#39;s smoking habits:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/22/11/29525943/snoop-dogg-microwaves-his-blunts-before-smoking-and-for-good-reason-heres-why">Snoop Dogg Microwaves His Blunts Before Smoking And For Good Reason, Here&#39;s Why</a></em></p>

<p>Snoop said he was speechless but then spoke up, declaring, &ldquo;one nation under a bud leaf...We gon&rsquo; blow one for the po&rsquo; one&rdquo; and pantomimed smoking a blunt.</p>

<p><em>Join the fun here!</em></p>

<p><iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FDzs7rIhti4?si=P_RmGeqPqKC44Uz8" width="560"></iframe></p>

<p><em>Photo: Shutterstock</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Accretion Acquisition Board Approved Extension Of Date By Which Company Would Be Required To Consummate A Business Combination To November 25, 2023</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/m-a/23/10/35358104/accretion-acquisition-board-approved-extension-of-date-by-which-company-would-be-required-to-consumm</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/m-a/23/10/35358104/accretion-acquisition-board-approved-extension-of-date-by-which-company-would-be-required-to-consumm</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:12:15 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>- SEC Filing</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dropbox Says A $28.1M Termination Payment Paid In Q4 Was Not Previously Factored Into Co's FY Free Cash Flow Guidance Range Of $820M-$840M</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358076/dropbox-says-a-28-1m-termination-payment-paid-in-q4-was-not-previously-factored-into-cos-fy-free-cas</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35358076/dropbox-says-a-28-1m-termination-payment-paid-in-q4-was-not-previously-factored-into-cos-fy-free-cas</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:09:57 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Entry into a Material Definitive Agreement.</strong></p><p>On October 17, 2023, Dropbox Inc. (the "Company") entered into a lease amendment (the "Amendment") to its Office Lease, dated October 6, 2017, as subsequently amended, with KRE Exchange Owner LLC (the "landlord") for its corporate headquarters in San Francisco, California, whereby the Company will surrender to the landlord 165,244 square feet of office space and pay an aggregate of $79.0 million in termination payments. The surrendering of space and payment of termination fees will occur in three tranches: 51,956 square feet and $28.1 million paid in the fourth quarter of 2023, 54,253 square feet and $14.9 million paid in the second quarter of 2024 and the remaining 59,035square feet and $36.0 million paid in the first quarter of 2025. As a result of the Amendment the Company will avoid future cash payments related to rent and common area maintenance fees of $137 million and approximately $90 million, respectively, over the remaining 10 year lease term.</p><p><br>&nbsp;</p><p>The foregoing description of the Amendment does not purport to be complete and is qualified in its entirety by reference to the text of the Amendment, a copy of which will be filed with the Company's Annual Report on Form 10-K for the year ending December 31, 2023.</p><p><br>&nbsp;</p><p><strong>Item 7.01 &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Regulation FD Disclosure</strong></p><p><br>&nbsp;</p><p>The $28.1 million termination payment paid in the fourth quarter of 2023 was not previously factored into the Company's stated full-year free cash flow guidance range of $820 million to $840 million (as previously provided in the investor supplement posted on the Company's investors.dropbox.com website on August 3, 2023). The Company intends to provide updated full-year free cash flow guidance during its third quarter 2023 financial results report on Thursday, November 2, 2023.</p><p><br>&nbsp;</p><p>The information contained in this Item 7.01 shall not be deemed "filed" for purposes of Section 18 of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934, as amended (the "Exchange Act") or otherwise subject to the liabilities of that section, nor shall it be deemed incorporated by reference in any filing under the Securities Act of 1933, as amended, or the Exchange Act, regardless of any general incorporation language in such filing.</p><p><br>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>FDA Approves BioMarin's VOXZOGO For Children Under 5 Years With Achondroplasia</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/general/biotech/23/10/35358063/fda-approves-biomarins-voxzogo-for-children-under-5-years-with-achondroplasia</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/general/biotech/23/10/35358063/fda-approves-biomarins-voxzogo-for-children-under-5-years-with-achondroplasia</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:09:11 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><i>Expanded Indication in the U.S. Now Includes Children of all ages with&nbsp;Achondroplasia</i></p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>BioMarin Pharmaceutical Inc. (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/BMRN#NASDAQ">BMRN</a>), a global biotechnology company dedicated to transforming lives through genetic discovery, today announced that the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) has approved the supplemental New Drug Application (sNDA) for VOXZOGO&#xAE; (vosoritide) to increase linear growth in pediatric patients with achondroplasia with open epiphyses (growth plates). This indication is approved under accelerated approval based on an improvement in annualized growth velocity. Previously, VOXZOGO was indicated for children who were 5 years of age and older. This expanded indication now includes children of all ages with open growth plates.</p><p>"We are pleased that VOXZOGO is now available for children of all ages with achondroplasia," said Hank Fuchs, M.D., president of Worldwide Research and Development at BioMarin. "We are grateful for the collaboration of the achondroplasia community, physicians, and the children and their families who have played a crucial role in advancing this clinical program. We also look forward to further understanding the potential role of VOXZOGO in other genetic short stature conditions, including hypochondroplasia."</p><p>"VOXZOGO is the only approved treatment for children with achondroplasia. Until now, it has only been approved in the U.S. for children aged 5 and older with open growth plates," said William Wilcox, M.D., professor of human genetics at Emory University. "I am delighted that VOXZOGO is now approved for younger children where we hope to have potentially greater impact by starting treatment earlier and, as a result, a much longer treatment window."</p><p>BioMarin conducted a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled Phase 2 clinical trial evaluating the safety and efficacy of VOXZOGO in children aged 5 and under (Study 111-206). Based on the results of this trial, together with evidence from the adequate and well controlled Phase 3 study in pediatric patients aged 5 years and older (Study 111-301), safety and effectiveness of VOXZOGO have been established in pediatric patients of all ages for the improvement in linear growth in children with achondroplasia with open epiphyses. The overall safety profile of VOXZOGO in children under 5 years of age was similar to that seen in older children.</p><p>Data from an open-label, long-term Phase 2 extension study was recently presented at the 2023 European Society for Paediatric Endocrinology Meeting in September. Over a four-year period, children aged 2 years and above who received VOXZOGO exhibited a mean (average) height Z-score improvement of 1.1 to 1.4 standard deviations (95% CI limits from 0.46 to 1.93) and a mean height gain of 6.3 to 7.8 centimeters (cm) (95% CI limits from 2.98 to 10.40 cm) when compared to untreated children with achondroplasia of the same age and sex. In addition, children under the age of 2 years, treated with VOXZOGO for three years, had a mean height Z-score improvement of 0.8 to 1.0 standard deviations (95% CI limits from 0.37 to 1.59) and a height gain between 3.5 and 3.9 cm (95% CI limits from 1.57 to 6.16 cm).</p><p>Since the introduction of VOXZOGO in 2021, the company has seen strong patient demand for the medicine worldwide. BioMarin has recently been able to secure increased fill-finish commitments in 2024 and beyond to meet this additional demand. There are approximately 800 children under 5 with achondroplasia in the U.S.</p><p>VOXZOGO is currently approved in Europe in children with achondroplasia who are 2 years of age and older with open growth plates. In September, the European Medicines Agency's (EMA) Committee for Medicinal Products for Human Use (CHMP) adopted a positive opinion recommending marketing authorization to expand the indication for VOXZOGO for injection to treat children with achondroplasia aged 4 months and older whose epiphyses are not closed. A final approval decision, typically consistent with the CHMP recommendation, is expected from the European Commission later this year. &nbsp;</p><p>VOXZOGO is also approved in Japan in children from birth who have achondroplasia with open growth plates. In addition, it is approved in Brazil in children who are 6 months and older with open growth plates&nbsp;as well as in Australia in children with achondroplasia who are 2 years of age and older with open growth plates.</p><p><strong>Orphan Drug Designation in Hypochondroplasia</strong></p><p>VOXZOGO also recently received orphan drug designation from the FDA for the treatment of hypochondroplasia, a genetic condition caused by a mutation in the fibroblast growth factor receptor 3 (FGFR3) gene and characterized by impaired bone growth. While similar to&nbsp;achondroplasia, people with hypochondroplasia typically present with milder disproportionality and less severe short stature compared to achondroplasia.</p><p>BioMarin plans to initiate a pivotal development program in hypochondroplasia later this year.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Investor Risk Sentiment Wavers Amid War, Interest Rate Concerns; Tesla Earnings Disappoint: The Week In The Markets</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/asia/23/10/35358005/investor-risk-sentiment-wavers-amid-war-interest-rate-concerns-tesla-earnings-disappoint-the-week-in</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/asia/23/10/35358005/investor-risk-sentiment-wavers-amid-war-interest-rate-concerns-tesla-earnings-disappoint-the-week-in</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:08:03 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Volatility notably returned to the markets this week as investors navigated the escalating conflict between Israel and Hamas, remarks from Federal Reserve Chair <strong>Jerome Powell </strong>and mixed earning reports <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/calendars/earnings">from leading U.S. corporations.</a></p>



<p><strong>Powell Says Fed Can Proceed &#8216;Carefully,&#8217; Warns Of Further Hikes If Data Remains Strong: </strong>During an event organized by the Economic Club of New York, Fed Chair <strong>Jerome Powell</strong> emphasized the need for a "careful" approach by the Federal Reserve that considers economic data. He also hinted that if the economy&#8217;s strength and inflation resurgence continue to surprise, further interest rate hikes may <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/bonds/23/10/35337404/powells-interest-rate-remarks-trigger-thursday-roller-coaster-what-did-fed-chair-say">be on the horizon</a>. It was a week marked by significant volatility in Treasuries, with yields reaching 5% on 10-year bonds. </p>



<p>Rising bond yields pressured major stock indices, with the <strong>SPDR S&amp;P 500 ETF Trust</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/SPY#NYSE">SPY</a>) down 2.3% and the tech-heavy <strong>Invesco QQQ Trust</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/QQQ#NASDAQ">QQQ</a>) down 3% for the week.</p>



<p>Among sectors, only the <strong>Energy Select Sector SPDR Fund</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/XLE#NYSE">XLE</a>) and the <strong>Consumer Staples</strong>&nbsp;<strong>Select Sector SPDR Fund</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/XLP#NYSE">XLP</a>) have remained unscathed, showing marginal gains. </p>



<p><strong>US Retail Sales Continue To Surpass Expectations, Defying Inflation, Interest Rates:</strong> In September, U.S. retail sales marked the sixth consecutive month of increases, underscoring consumers&#8217; remarkable resilience despite rising inflation and higher interest rates. On an annual basis, retail sales surged by 3.8%, up from the upwardly revised 2.9% recorded in August, marking the most substantial year-over-year <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35286199/september-retail-sales-top-expectations-as-consumers-defy-high-inflation-interest">gain since February 2023</a>.</p>



<p><strong>Tesla Reports Lower-Than-Expected Q3 Results, Stock Faces Worst Week Of 2023:</strong> <strong>Tesla Inc.</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TSLA#NASDAQ">TSLA</a>) reported third-quarter earnings and revenue below expectations. Revenue reached $23.35 billion, a 9% increase from the previous year but falling short of the Street&#8217;s $24.38-billion estimate. Adjusted earnings per share came in at 66 cents, also missing predictions. The company announced plans to commence deliveries of the <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35318136/tesla-q3-earnings-highlights-revenue-miss-eps-miss-cybertruck-launch-set-for-november-and-more">new Cybertruck in November.</a> Tesla&#8217;s stock experienced a 15.2% decline for the week, marking its worst weekly performance this year.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Chart: Tesla Faces Worst Weekly Performance In 2023</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1024" height="708" src="https://editorial-assets.benzinga.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/20154644/TSLA_2023-10-20_17-18-23_7377a-1024x708.png" alt="" class="wp-image-128088" srcset="https://editorial-assets.benzinga.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/20154644/TSLA_2023-10-20_17-18-23_7377a-1024x708.png 1024w,https://editorial-assets.benzinga.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/20154644/TSLA_2023-10-20_17-18-23_7377a-300x208.png 300w,https://editorial-assets.benzinga.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/20154644/TSLA_2023-10-20_17-18-23_7377a-768x531.png 768w,https://editorial-assets.benzinga.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/20154644/TSLA_2023-10-20_17-18-23_7377a-1536x1063.png 1536w,https://editorial-assets.benzinga.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/20154644/TSLA_2023-10-20_17-18-23_7377a.png 1561w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><strong>Netflix Surpasses Expectations With Q3 Report: Netflix Inc. </strong>(NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/NFLX#NASDAQ">NFLX</a>) achieved a remarkable earnings and revenue beat in the third quarter, reporting earnings of $3.73 per share compared to the expected $3.49. As a result, Netflix shares saw double-digit gains for the week, making it one of the S&amp;P 500&#8217;s top weekly performers.</p>



<p><strong>Gold Attracts Haven Demand, Miners Outshine Other Sectors:</strong> Gold has emerged as one of the top-performing assets since the onset of the conflict in Israel, with the <strong>SPDR Gold Trust ETF </strong>(NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/GLD#NYSE">GLD</a>) showing a nearly 10% increase, solidifying its position as a safe haven investment. Silver has also risen in harmony. Among equities, gold mining stocks, as tracked by the <strong>VanEck Gold Miners ETF</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/GDX#NYSE">GDX</a>) have outshone all other industries, capitalizing on the surge <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/23/10/35318074/gold-miners-positioned-for-upswing-keep-an-eye-on-this-leading-economic-indicator">in precious metal prices</a>.</p>



<p><strong>What To Watch In The Week Ahead:</strong> On Thursday, the highly anticipated GDP data for the third quarter will be released, with economists predicting a robust 4.1% annualized growth rate. Friday will bring the release of the Federal Reserve&#8217;s preferred inflation gauge, the Personal Consumption Expenditure (PCE) index, for September. The headline PCE index is expected to show a decline from 3.7% year-on-year to 3.6%. </p>



<p><strong>Upcoming Corporate Earnings to Watch:</strong> Tuesday features a lineup of major companies including <strong>Microsoft Corporation</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/MSFT#NASDAQ">MSFT</a>), <strong>Alphabet Inc.</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/GOOGL#NASDAQ">GOOGL</a>) (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/GOOG#NASDAQ">GOOG</a>), <strong>Visa Inc.</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/V#NYSE">V</a>), <strong>The Coca-Cola Company</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/KO#NYSE">KO</a>), <strong>Danaher Corporation</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/DHR#NYSE">DHR</a>), <strong>Texas Instruments Incorporated</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TXN#NASDAQ">TXN</a>), <strong>Verizon Communications Inc.</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/VZ#NYSE">VZ</a>), <strong>General Electric Company</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/GE#NYSE">GE</a>) and <strong>Raytheon Technologies Corporation</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/RTX#NYSE">RTX</a>).</p>



<p>Wednesday will bring earnings reports from <strong>Meta Platforms, Inc.</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/FB#NASDAQ">FB</a>), <strong>Thermo Fisher Scientific Inc.</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TMO#NYSE">TMO</a>), <strong>T-Mobile US, Inc.</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TMUS#NASDAQ">TMUS</a>), <strong>International Business Machines Corporation</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/IBM#NYSE">IBM</a>), <strong>ServiceNow, Inc.</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/NOW#NYSE">NOW</a>), <strong>The Boeing Company</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/BA#NYSE">BA</a>), <strong>Automatic Data Processing, Inc.</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/ADP#NASDAQ">ADP</a>) and <strong>CME Group Inc.</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/CME#NASDAQ">CME</a>).</p>



<p>Thursday includes <strong>Amazon.com, Inc.</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/AMZN#NASDAQ">AMZN</a>), <strong>Mastercard Incorporated</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/MA#NYSE">MA</a>), <strong>Merck &amp; Co., Inc.</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/MRK#NYSE">MRK</a>), <strong>Comcast Corporation</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/CMCSA#NASDAQ">CMCSA</a>), <strong>Intel Corporation</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/INTC#NASDAQ">INTC</a>), <strong>Caterpillar Inc.</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/CAT#NYSE">CAT</a>), <strong>United Parcel Service, Inc.</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/UPS#NYSE">UPS</a>), <strong>Honeywell International Inc.</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/HON#NASDAQ">HON</a>) and <strong>Bristol-Myers Squibb Company</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/BMY#NYSE">BMY</a>).</p>



<p>Friday will wrap up the week with reports from <strong>Exxon Mobil Corporation</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/XOM#NYSE">XOM</a>), <strong>Chevron Corporation</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/CVX#NYSE">CVX</a>) and <strong>AbbVie Inc.</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/ABBV#NYSE">ABBV</a>).</p>



<p><em>Now read: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/etfs/broad-u-s-equity-etfs/23/10/35357397/hamas-releases-2-american-hostages-amid-escalating-tensions-calls-for-ceasefire-grow">Hamas Releases 2 American Hostages Amid Escalating Tensions: Calls For Ceasefire Grow</a></em></p>



<p><em>Photo via Shutterstock. </em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bitcoin Shoots Higher, Pulls Ethereum, Dogecoin North: A Look At The Cryptos Into The Weekend</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356368/bitcoin-shoots-higher-pulls-ethereum-dogecoin-north-a-look-at-the-cryptos-into-the-weekend</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356368/bitcoin-shoots-higher-pulls-ethereum-dogecoin-north-a-look-at-the-cryptos-into-the-weekend</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:08:02 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Bitcoin</strong> (CRYPTO: <a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/btc/usd">BTC</a>) was leading the crypto sector higher during Friday&rsquo;s 24-hour trading session amid optimism that the approval of a<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35349102/bitcoin-breaches-30-000-for-first-time-since-august-whats-driving-the-surge"> spot Bitcoin ETF is on the horizon</a>.</p>

<p><strong>BlackRock</strong> and <strong>Fidelity</strong> introduced changes to their spot Bitcoin ETF submissions at the beginning of the week, while <strong>Grayscale</strong> filed an S-3 application as part of its efforts to secure similar approvals.</p>

<p>From a technical analysis perspective, Bitcoin was attempting to break up from a triple inside bar pattern. Ethereum and Dogecoin were unable to break up above their Oct. 16 high, causing the cryptos to remain trading in symmetrical triangle patterns.</p>

<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/money/stock-chart-patterns">A symmetrical triangle pattern</a> is created when a stock forms a series of lower highs and higher lows between a descending and an ascending trendline, which meet on the right side of the chart to form an apex. The pattern indicates that the bulls and bears are equally in control.</p>

<p>A symmetrical triangle is often formed on lower-than-average volume and demonstrates a decrease in volatility, indicating consolidation. The decreasing volume is often followed by a sharp increase in volume when the stock breaks up or down from the pattern, which should happen before the stock reaches the apex of the triangle.</p>

<p><em>Want direct analysis? Find me in the BZ Pro lounge! <a href="https://benzinga.grsm.io/1ih7p9hphj9p">Click here for a free trial</a>.</em></p>

<p><strong>The Bitcoin Chart:</strong> For the last three trading days, Bitcoin&rsquo;s trading range has taken place within the Oct. 16 mother bar, which settled the crypto into a triple inside bar pattern. The pattern leans bullish for continuation because Bitcoin has been trading in a strong uptrend.</p>

<p>During Friday&rsquo;s trading session, Bitcoin temporarily broke above the top of the mother bar but ran into a group of sellers near $30,000, which caused a retracement. The spike caused Bitcoin to form another higher high, however, which confirmed&nbsp;the uptrend remains intact.</p>

<p>When Bitcoin surged on Oct. 16, the crypto regained support at the 200-day simple moving average (SMA), which indicates Bitcoin is trading in a bull cycle. If Bitcoin can remain above the 200-day SMA for a period of time, the 50-day SMA will cross above the 200-day, which would cause a golden cross to form.</p>

<p>A loss of the 200-day SMA on big bearish volume could be an exit signal for bullish traders holding a position.</p>

<p>Bitcoin has resistance above at $30,050 and at $31,418 and support below at $28,690 and at $27,133.</p>

<p><img alt="screenshot_61.png" src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/u278075/screenshot_61.png" style="height:427px; width:760px" /><strong>The Ethereum and Dogecoin Charts:</strong> Ethereum and Dogecoin began trading in symmetrical triangle patterns on Oct. 3 and Oct. 2, respectively. The patterns lean bearish in this case but the upward trajectory of Bitcoin may cause Ethereum and Dogecoin to break bullishly from the formation.,</p>

<p>Ethereum and Dogecoin have both been making a series of higher lows and lower highs as their trading range tightens. When the cryptos attempted to break up from the triangles, Ethereum and Dogecoin both rejected the 50-day SMA, indicating the cryptos are trading in bear cycles.</p>

<p>Bullish traders want to see Ethereum and Dogecoin regain the 50-day SMA as support, which will also cause the cryptos to break up from their triangles. Bearish traders want to see big bearish volume come in and cause the cryptos to break down from the triangles, which will throw Ethereum and Dogecoin into downtrends.</p>

<p>Ethereum has resistance above at $1,615 and at $1,717 and support below at $1,564 and at $1,421.</p>

<p><img alt="screenshot_62.png" src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/u278075/screenshot_62.png" style="height:427px; width:760px" />Dogecoin has resistance above at $0.061 and at $0.065 and support below at $0. 057 and at $0.055.</p>

<p><img alt="screenshot_63.png" src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/u278075/screenshot_63.png" style="height:427px; width:760px" /><em>Find out what the experts have to say on the evolving crypto space. Meet and engage with other transformative&nbsp;</em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/go/crypto-conference-article-link" target="_blank"><em>Digital Asset and Crypto</em></a><em>&nbsp;business leaders and investors at Benzinga&#39;s exclusive event:&nbsp;</em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/go/crypto-conference-article-link" target="_blank"><em>Future of Digital Assets</em></a><em>. Tickets are flying:&nbsp;</em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/go/crypto-conference-article-link" target="_blank"><em>Get yours</em></a><em>!&nbsp;&nbsp;</em></p>

<p><em>Read Next:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35332465/meet-web3-trendsetter-william-e-quigley-at-benzingas-future-of-digital-assets-event">Meet Web3 Trendsetter William E. Quigley At Benzinga&#39;s Future Of Digital Assets Event</a></em></p>

<p><em>Photo: Shutterstock</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>XTL Biopharmaceuticals Confirms That It Has Not Experienced Any Disruption To Its Business Operations In Israel</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35357793/xtl-biopharmaceuticals-confirms-that-it-has-not-experienced-any-disruption-to-its</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35357793/xtl-biopharmaceuticals-confirms-that-it-has-not-experienced-any-disruption-to-its</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:01:34 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>XTL's management confirms that to date the Company has not seen any adverse impact to its ongoing operations in Israel and continues to work as normal. At the same time, the Company continues to monitor its ongoing activities and make any needed adjustments to ensure a smooth continuity of its business. The Company notes that its headquarters are in the center of the country, near Tel Aviv, and not near any borders.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Here's How Much $100 Invested In Starbucks 20 Years Ago Would Be Worth Today</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357765/heres-how-much-100-invested-in-starbucks-20-years-ago-would-be-worth-today</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357765/heres-how-much-100-invested-in-starbucks-20-years-ago-would-be-worth-today</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:00:58 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Starbucks (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/SBUX#NASDAQ">SBUX</a>) has outperformed the market over the past 20 years by 6.11% on an annualized basis producing an average annual return of 13.3%. Currently, Starbucks has a market capitalization of $108.35 billion. </p>
<p><strong>Buying $100 In SBUX:</strong> If an investor had bought $100 of SBUX stock 20 years ago, it would be worth <strong>$1,255.45</strong> today based on a price of $94.60 for SBUX at the time of writing.</p>
<h3>Starbucks's Performance Over Last 20 Years</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697832055_0.png" alt="comp_fig" /></p>

<p>Finally -- what's the point of all this? The key insight to take from this article is to note how much of a difference compounded returns can make in your cash growth over a period of time.</p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Analyst Expectations for Equifax's Future</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357762/analyst-expectations-for-equifaxs-future</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357762/analyst-expectations-for-equifaxs-future</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:00:55 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Within the last quarter, Equifax (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/EFX#NYSE">EFX</a>) has observed the following analyst ratings: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>According to 6 analyst offering 12-month price targets in the last 3 months, Equifax has an average price target of $206.5 with a high of $230.00 and a low of $195.00. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 6 analysts rated Equifax over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697832051_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average represents a 10.3% decrease from the previous average price target of $230.20. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/EFX/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Equifax analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>What Are Analyst Ratings?</h1>
<p>Analysts are specialists within banking and financial systems that typically report for specific stocks or within defined sectors. These people research company financial statements, sit in conference calls and meetings, and speak with relevant insiders to determine what are known as analyst ratings for stocks. Typically, analysts will rate each stock once a quarter. </p>
<p>Some analysts also offer predictions for helpful metrics such as earnings, revenue, and growth estimates to provide further guidance as to what to do with certain tickers. It is important to keep in mind that while stock and sector analysts are specialists, they are also human and can only forecast their beliefs to traders.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>General Electric Unusual Options Activity</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/options/23/10/35357757/general-electric-unusual-options-activity</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/options/23/10/35357757/general-electric-unusual-options-activity</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:00:50 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>A whale with a lot of money to spend has taken a noticeably bullish stance on <strong>General Electric</strong>.</p>
<p>Looking at options history for General Electric (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/GE#NYSE">GE</a>) we detected 11 strange trades.</p>
<p>If we consider the specifics of each trade, it is accurate to state that 63% of the investors opened trades with bullish expectations and 36% with bearish.</p>
<p>From the overall spotted trades, 3 are puts, for a total amount of $1,165,100 and 8, calls, for a total amount of $442,875.</p>
<h3>What's The Price Target?</h3>
<p>Taking into account the Volume and Open Interest on these contracts, it appears that whales have been targeting a price range from $100.0 to $145.0 for General Electric over the last 3 months. </p>
<h3>Volume &amp; Open Interest Development</h3>
<p>In terms of liquidity and interest, the mean open interest for General Electric options trades today is 1603.78 with a total volume of 2,613.00.</p>
<p>In the following chart, we are able to follow the development of volume and open interest of call and put options for General Electric's big money trades within a strike price range of $100.0 to $145.0 over the last 30 days.</p>
<h3>General Electric Option Volume And Open Interest Over Last 30 Days</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697832046_0.png" alt="Options Call Chart" /></p>

<h3>Biggest Options Spotted:</h3>
<p><table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th><strong>Symbol</strong></th>
<th><strong>PUT/CALL</strong></th>
<th><strong>Trade Type</strong></th>
<th><strong>Sentiment</strong></th>
<th><strong>Exp. Date</strong></th>
<th><strong>Strike Price</strong></th>
<th><strong>Total Trade Price</strong></th>
<th><strong>Open Interest</strong></th>
<th><strong>Volume</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>GE</td>
<td>PUT</td>
<td>TRADE</td>
<td>NEUTRAL</td>
<td>01/19/24</td>
<td>$105.00</td>
<td>$1.1M</td>
<td>2.8K</td>
<td>2.0K</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>GE</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BULLISH</td>
<td>09/20/24</td>
<td>$105.00</td>
<td>$228.3K</td>
<td>89</td>
<td>1</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>GE</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BULLISH</td>
<td>10/20/23</td>
<td>$100.00</td>
<td>$38.6K</td>
<td>147</td>
<td>16</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>GE</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BEARISH</td>
<td>01/17/25</td>
<td>$145.00</td>
<td>$35.6K</td>
<td>312</td>
<td>99</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>GE</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BULLISH</td>
<td>01/19/24</td>
<td>$110.00</td>
<td>$29.3K</td>
<td>3.0K</td>
<td>64</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table></p>
<h3>Where Is General Electric Standing Right Now?</h3>
<ul>
<li>With a volume of 3,911,290, the price of GE is down -0.66% at $106.24. </li>
<li>RSI indicators hint that the underlying stock may be approaching oversold.</li>
<li>Next earnings are expected to be released in 4 days.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What The Experts Say On General Electric:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Deutsche Bank downgraded its action to Buy with a price target of $141</li>
</ul>
<p>Options are a riskier asset compared to just trading the stock, but they have higher profit potential. Serious options traders manage this risk by educating themselves daily, scaling in and out of trades, following more than one indicator, and following the markets closely.</p>
<p>If you want to stay updated on the latest options trades for General Electric, <a href="https://benzinga.grsm.io/register174">Benzinga Pro</a> gives you real-time options trades alerts.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>8 Analysts Have This to Say About Alcoa</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357756/8-analysts-have-this-to-say-about-alcoa</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357756/8-analysts-have-this-to-say-about-alcoa</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:00:47 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past 3 months, 8 analysts have published their opinion on Alcoa (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/AA#NYSE">AA</a>) stock. These analysts are typically employed by large Wall Street banks and tasked with understanding a company's business to predict how a stock will trade over the upcoming year.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">4</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>These 8 analysts have an average price target of $29.88 versus the current price of Alcoa at $23.5, implying  upside.</p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 8 analysts rated Alcoa over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697832043_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average has decreased by 14.01% from the previous average price target of $34.75. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/AA/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Alcoa analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>Analyst Ratings: What Are They?</h1>
<p>Benzinga tracks 150 analyst firms and reports on their stock expectations. Analysts typically arrive at their conclusions by predicting how much money a company will make in the future, usually the upcoming five years, and how risky or predictable that company's revenue streams are.</p>
<p>Analysts attend company conference calls and meetings, research company financial statements, and communicate with insiders to publish their ratings on stocks. Analysts typically rate each stock once per quarter or whenever the company has a major update.</p>
<p>Some analysts publish their predictions for metrics such as growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide additional guidance with their ratings. When using analyst ratings, it is important to keep in mind that stock and sector analysts are also human and are only offering their opinions to investors.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Latest Analyst Ratings for Commerce Bancshares</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357750/the-latest-analyst-ratings-for-commerce-bancshares</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357750/the-latest-analyst-ratings-for-commerce-bancshares</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:00:40 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Within the last quarter, Commerce Bancshares (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/CBSH#NASDAQ">CBSH</a>) has observed the following analyst ratings: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>These 4 analysts have an average price target of $49.5 versus the current price of Commerce Bancshares at $45.35, implying  upside.</p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 4 analysts rated Commerce Bancshares over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697832036_0_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average has decreased by 1.0% from the previous average price target of $50.00. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/CBSH/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Commerce Bancshares analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>Analyst Ratings: What Are They?</h1>
<p>Ratings come from analysts, or specialists within banking and financial systems that report for specific stocks or defined sectors (typically once per quarter for each stock). Analysts usually derive their information from company conference calls and meetings, financial statements, and conversations with important insiders to reach their decisions.</p>
<p>Some analysts publish their predictions for metrics such as growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide additional guidance with their ratings. When using analyst ratings, it is important to keep in mind that stock and sector analysts are also human and are only offering their opinions to investors.</p>
<p>If you want to keep track of which analysts are outperforming others, you can view updated analyst ratings along withanalyst success scores in <a href="https://benzinga.grsm.io/register174">Benzinga Pro</a>.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>What 5 Analyst Ratings Have To Say About Marqeta</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357743/what-5-analyst-ratings-have-to-say-about-marqeta</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357743/what-5-analyst-ratings-have-to-say-about-marqeta</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:00:33 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Within the last quarter, Marqeta (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/MQ#NASDAQ">MQ</a>) has observed the following analyst ratings: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>In the last 3 months, 5 analysts have offered 12-month price targets for Marqeta. The company has an average price target of $6.7 with a high of $8.00 and a low of $4.00. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 5 analysts rated Marqeta over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697832030_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average has increased by 18.17% from the previous average price target of $5.67. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/MQ/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Marqeta analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>Analyst Ratings: What Are They?</h1>
<p>Benzinga tracks 150 analyst firms and reports on their stock expectations. Analysts typically arrive at their conclusions by predicting how much money a company will make in the future, usually the upcoming five years, and how risky or predictable that company's revenue streams are.</p>
<p>Analysts attend company conference calls and meetings, research company financial statements, and communicate with insiders to publish their ratings on stocks. Analysts typically rate each stock once per quarter or whenever the company has a major update.</p>
<p>Some analysts publish their predictions for metrics such as growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide additional guidance with their ratings. When using analyst ratings, it is important to keep in mind that stock and sector analysts are also human and are only offering their opinions to investors.</p>
<p>If you want to keep track of which analysts are outperforming others, you can view updated analyst ratings along withanalyst success scores in <a href="https://benzinga.grsm.io/register174">Benzinga Pro</a>.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Earnings Preview For Dynex Cap</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35357742/earnings-preview-for-dynex-cap</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35357742/earnings-preview-for-dynex-cap</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:00:32 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Dynex Cap</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/DX#NYSE">DX</a>) is set to give its latest quarterly earnings report on Monday, 2023-10-23. Here's what investors need to know before the announcement.</p>
<p>Analysts estimate that Dynex Cap will report an <strong>earnings per share</strong> (EPS) of $-0.17. </p>
<p>Dynex Cap bulls will hope to hear the company announce they've not only beaten that estimate, but also to provide positive guidance, or forecasted growth, for the next quarter.</p>
<p>New investors should note that it is sometimes not an earnings beat or miss that most affects the price of a stock, but the guidance (or forecast).</p>
<h3>Historical Earnings Performance</h3>
<p>Last quarter the company missed EPS by $0.30, which was followed by a 1.52% increase in the share price the next day.</p>
<p>Here's a look at Dynex Cap's past performance and the resulting price change:</p>
<p><table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th><strong>Quarter</strong></th>
<th><strong>Q2 2023</strong></th>
<th><strong>Q1 2023</strong></th>
<th><strong>Q4 2022</strong></th>
<th><strong>Q3 2022</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>EPS Estimate</strong></td>
<td>0.03</td>
<td>0.15</td>
<td>0.20</td>
<td>0.32</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>EPS Actual</strong></td>
<td>-0.27</td>
<td>-0.16</td>
<td>0.03</td>
<td>0.24</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Price Change %</strong></td>
<td>1.52%</td>
<td>-0.6%</td>
<td>1.91%</td>
<td>4.28%</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table></p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697832028_0.png" alt="eps graph" /></p>

<h3>Stock Performance</h3>
<p>Shares of Dynex Cap were trading at $10.8 as of October 19. Over the last 52-week period, shares are down 2.32%. Given that these returns are generally negative, long-term shareholders are likely a little upset going into this earnings release. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/DX/earnings"><strong>To track all earnings releases for Dynex Cap visit their earnings calendar on our site.</strong></a></p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Analyst Ratings for Toast</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357741/analyst-ratings-for-toast</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357741/analyst-ratings-for-toast</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:00:26 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Toast (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TOST#NYSE">TOST</a>) has observed the following analyst ratings within the last quarter: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">4</td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">6</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>According to 13 analyst offering 12-month price targets in the last 3 months, Toast has an average price target of $25.54 with a high of $31.00 and a low of $16.00. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 13 analysts rated Toast over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697832022_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average has decreased by 1.96% from the previous average price target of $26.05. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/TOST/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Toast analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>Analyst Ratings: What Are They?</h1>
<p>Benzinga tracks 150 analyst firms and reports on their stock expectations. Analysts typically arrive at their conclusions by predicting how much money a company will make in the future, usually the upcoming five years, and how risky or predictable that company's revenue streams are.</p>
<p>Analysts attend company conference calls and meetings, research company financial statements, and communicate with insiders to publish their ratings on stocks. Analysts typically rate each stock once per quarter or whenever the company has a major update.</p>
<p>Some analysts publish their predictions for metrics such as growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide additional guidance with their ratings. When using analyst ratings, it is important to keep in mind that stock and sector analysts are also human and are only offering their opinions to investors.</p>
<p>If you want to keep track of which analysts are outperforming others, you can view updated analyst ratings along withanalyst success scores in <a href="https://benzinga.grsm.io/register174">Benzinga Pro</a>.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Latest Analyst Ratings for Flywire</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357728/the-latest-analyst-ratings-for-flywire</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35357728/the-latest-analyst-ratings-for-flywire</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 16:00:17 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past 3 months, 11 analysts have published their opinion on Flywire (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/FLYW#NASDAQ">FLYW</a>) stock. These analysts are typically employed by large Wall Street banks and tasked with understanding a company's business to predict how a stock will trade over the upcoming year.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">6</td>
<td align="right">4</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>According to 11 analyst offering 12-month price targets in the last 3 months, Flywire has an average price target of $39.09 with a high of $44.00 and a low of $32.00. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 11 analysts rated Flywire over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697832014_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average has increased by 12.62% from the previous average price target of $34.71. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/FLYW/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Flywire analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>How Are Analyst Ratings Determined?</h1>
<p>Benzinga tracks 150 analyst firms and reports on their stock expectations. Analysts typically arrive at their conclusions by predicting how much money a company will make in the future, usually the upcoming five years, and how risky or predictable that company's revenue streams are.</p>
<p>Analysts attend company conference calls and meetings, research company financial statements, and communicate with insiders to publish their ratings on stocks. Analysts typically rate each stock once per quarter or whenever the company has a major update.</p>
<p>Some analysts will also offer forecasts for metrics like growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide further guidance on stocks. Investors who use analyst ratings should note that this specialized advice comes from humans and may be subject to error.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>'Biden To Host First-Of-Its-Kind Americas Summit To Address Immigration Struggles; Biden Will Host Leaders From Western Hemisphere At White House On November 3' - CBS News</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35357683/biden-to-host-first-of-its-kind-americas-summit-to-address-immigration-struggles-</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35357683/biden-to-host-first-of-its-kind-americas-summit-to-address-immigration-struggles-</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:59:31 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/biden-to-host-immigration-amricas-summit-november/#:~:text=The%20Americas%20Summit%20is%20set,White%20House%20tells%20CBS%20News.">https://www.cbsnews.com/news/biden-to-host-immigration-amricas-summit-november/#:~:text=The%20Americas%20Summit%20is%20set,White%20House%20tells%20CBS%20News.</a></p><p><br><a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/politics?ftag=CNM-16-10abg0d"><strong>POLITICS</strong></a></p><h2><strong>Biden to host first-of-its-kind Americas summit to address immigration struggles</strong></h2><p><strong>BY MARGARET BRENNAN, ED O'KEEFE</strong></p><p><strong>UPDATED ON: OCTOBER 20, 2023 / 3:34 PM / CBS NEWS</strong></p><ul><li>&nbsp;</li><li>&nbsp;</li><li>&nbsp;</li></ul><p>President Biden is set to host a first-of-its-kind summit with representatives of 11 countries next month to address the hemisphere's growing immigration struggles.&nbsp;</p><p>The Americas Summit is set to be held Nov. 3 in Washington and hosted by the president, who has invited leaders of Barbados, Canada, Chile, Colombia, Costa Rica, the Dominican Republic, Ecuador, Mexico, Panama, Peru and Uruguay to attend, the White House tells CBS News. &nbsp;</p><p>The countries are members of the Americas Partnership for Economic Prosperity (APEP), launched last year at the Summit of the Americas in Los Angeles to address concerns about economic development, inequality, and the fate of hemisphere's democracies. &nbsp;</p><p>A senior administration official said in a statement that the summit would provide an opportunity to deepen economic integration among western hemisphere countries. The official said the aim of the summit is to "drive more inclusive and sustainable economic growth, and tackle the underlying economic drivers of irregular migration in our hemisphere."</p><p>During the summit, leaders are expected to establish three discrete tracks, in finance, trade and foreign affairs, for countries to quickly begin to set specific goals and the processes to start executing them, the official also said.</p><p>The gathering comes as the <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/biden-100-billion-request-congress-ukraine-israel/">president is asking Congress for roughly $6.4 billion</a> to shore up border security programs, a response to growing bipartisan concerns on Capitol Hill, plus notable public ire from Democratic governors and big-city mayors about how the Biden administration is struggling to respond to a record-setting number of illegal border crossings. Republican presidential candidates continue to criticize the Biden administration's immigration and border security policies  Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis has even called for the use of U.S. military forces along the southern border to keep drug cartels from smuggling across fentanyl and other illegal drugs.&nbsp;</p><p>A record&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/venezuelan-migrants-us-mexico-border-september-numbers/">approximately 50,000 migrants from crisis-stricken Venezuela</a>&nbsp;crossed the U.S.-Mexico border in September, while thousands are still coming from El Salvador, Guatemala, Honduras, Mexico and other countries. In response, the Biden administration this week&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/u-s-venezuela-deportations-reduce-record-border-arrivals/">restarted direct deportations to Venezuela</a>, resuming a practice suspended amid strained relations with the government of the country's leader, Nicolas Maduro. Amid a widespread economic crisis, Venezuelans are leaving their homeland in record numbers, the largest refugee exodus recorded in the Western Hemisphere according to the United Nations.&nbsp;</p><p>But this week, Maduro's government and representatives of opposition parties agreed to restart negotiations that could lead to free presidential elections next year and the release of political prisoners, moves that could prompt the Biden administration to ease sanctions on the country's oil industry. That relief is also dependent on whether Maduro follows through with the release of three Americans  Eyvin Hernandez, Jerrel Kenemore, and Joseph Cristella  who are classified by the State Department as "wrongfully detained."&nbsp;</p><p>The emergency spending request submitted Friday by the White House to Congress asks for $4.4 billion for the Department of Homeland Security to build new immigrant holding facilities and to reimburse the Pentagon for military support along the border.&nbsp;</p><p>The administration's request includes a $1.9 billion ask for the Department of Health and Human Service's ongoing care and support for unaccompanied migrant children and families, plus a $204 million request to pay for a Trump-era policy requiring the Justice Department to collect DNA samples from hundreds of thousands of asylum-seekers and migrants crossing annually. &nbsp;</p><p>It is not yet clear if the leaders of all 11 countries plan to attend the summit, but invitations to various events to be held on the sidelines of the summit began circulating around Washington this week. The meetings are the brainchild of Christopher J. Dodd, a special presidential adviser for the Americas whose State Department perch gives him wide latitude over western hemisphere policy. A longtime friend of the president and former Peace Corps volunteer in the Dominican Republic, he's one of the most seasoned American policymakers on Latin America. &nbsp;</p><p>Leaders of El Salvador, Guatemala and Honduras  three countries from whom tens of thousands of people have fled in recent years and through which tens of thousands of others must traverse on their way to Mexico and the United States  were not invited to the summit because they did not join the APEP accords last year, according to diplomats familiar with the planning. All three countries have frosty relations with the Biden administration given concerns about a loosening of democratic norms and tougher law enforcement policies that have led to the wrongful imprisonment of thousands of people, especially in El Salvador.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Marijuana Magic: 93% Of Athletes Say Cannabis Aids Recovery</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35039103/marijuana-magic-93-of-athletes-say-cannabis-aids-recovery</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35039103/marijuana-magic-93-of-athletes-say-cannabis-aids-recovery</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:57:37 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>This article was originally published on <a href="https://cannabis.net/blog/medical/athletes-say-cannabis-is-best-for-exercise-recovery-lactic-acid-build-up-and-muscle-repair-acco">Cannabis.net</a> and appears here with permission.</p>

<p>For&nbsp;<a href="https://cannabis.net/blog/sports/athletes-who-train-with-cannabis-win-gold">athletes</a>, proper rest and recovery is just as important for overall&nbsp;<a href="https://cannabis.net/blog/sports/how-cbd-can-improve-athletic-performance">health and performance</a>&nbsp;as training.</p>

<p>Athletes can benefit from both passive and active recovery. Aside from these, getting enough sleep is critical because lack of sleep can significantly affect your performance for several days. These practices work together to help athletes perform their best while ensuring they stay healthy from the inside out. That&rsquo;s because&nbsp;<a href="https://cannabis.net/blog/medical/top-cannabis-strains-for-exercise-and-recovery">recovery</a>&nbsp;is necessary for the well-being of athletes, and just about anyone who exercises regularly.</p>

<p>There are several tools that can&nbsp;<a href="https://cannabis.net/blog/medical/5-ways-cbd-can-boost-the-athletic-side-of-you">help athletes</a>&nbsp;recover more efficiently. Over the past few years, there has been a growing interest among athletes and sports circles in the use of marijuana products for recovery. It&rsquo;s been backed up by studies, too.</p>

<p>A&nbsp;<a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC10403841/">recent study</a>&nbsp;conducted by Kent State University researchers involved polling more than 100 participants who used cannabis while regularly performing resistance and/or aerobic training. The data, which was published in the medical journal, the Journal of Cannabis Research, revealed that <a href="https://elplanteo.com/aceite-cbd-ansiedad/">cannabidiol</a> (CBD) as well as tetrahydrocannabinol (THC) was found to be helpful for athletes in recovery.</p>

<p class="core-block"><em class="core-block"><strong class="core-block">See also: <a class="core-block" href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/21/11/23825005/study-shows-cannabis-consumers-are-successful-motivated-health-conscious-snoop-dogg-weighs-in" target="_blank">Snoop Dogg Shatters Cannabis Clich&eacute;s: Consumers Are Highly Educated, Successful, Motivated</a></strong></em></p>

<p>&ldquo;Twenty-two participants (20%) reported using CBD for recovery from aerobic exercise and 25 participants (23%) reported CBD use to recover from resistance exercise,&rdquo; they wrote. Around 60% of them also used THC for the same purpose. When the participants were polled on whether they felt that cannabis was helpful for recovery, a majority of them answered yes (93%).</p>

<p>On the other hand, a majority of respondents who consumed THC said that it was used for the &ldquo;pleasant feelings&rdquo; it evoked as well as for fun and relaxation. They did say that they experienced side effects from using THC, which for them meant getting too high, uncontrollable laughter, sleepiness, and heart racing.</p>

<p>&ldquo;The present study demonstrated that in addition to more traditional recovery methods, cannabis use is an ergogenic recovery aid by individuals that exercise regularly&hellip; More data are necessary to understand the role of cannabis in exercise recovery as well as perceived ergogenic benefits of cannabis by individuals who both regularly participate in exercise and habitually use cannabis,&rdquo; concluded the authors.</p>

<p>Meanwhile,&nbsp;<a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37440169/#article-details">another study</a>&nbsp;whose results were published in July 2023 in Cannabis and Cannabinoid Research found that marijuana-consuming runners experienced a great improvement in their performance and even recovery because of pot. According to the authors, since marijuana use together with exercise has been attracting attention over the last few years, it has effectively contradicted the famous stereotype that marijuana users are lazy and sedentary. Because of this, they wanted to have a better understanding of the link between exercise and cannabis use by comparing the experiences of runners who consumed legal cannabis and non-using runners.</p>

<p>Forty-nine marijuana-consuming subjects whose ages ranged from 21 to 49 were then analyzed. They found that 3.88 miles was the average distance both groups ran. &ldquo;Although participants ran an average of 31 seconds/mile slower during their cannabis run, this difference was not statistically significant,&rdquo; they wrote. However, subjects &ldquo;reported lower pain levels after their cannabis run,&rdquo; they wrote.</p>

<p><em><strong>See also: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/biotech/23/10/35316350/nobel-prize-winner-views-medical-cannabis-as-a-real-therapeutic-treatment-free-of-mysticism">Nobel Prize Winner Views Medical Cannabis As &#39;A Real Therapeutic Treatment...Free Of Mysticism&#39;</a></strong></em></p>

<p>&ldquo;Results suggest that acute cannabis use may be associated with a more positive exercise experience among regular cannabis users. Research using varied methodologies, a range of exercise modalities, and diverse populations is needed to establish the long-term harms and benefits associated with this behavior, as well as the generalizability of these findings to other populations and settings,&rdquo; the authors concluded.</p>

<p><strong>How Else Can Weed Positively Impact Your Workout?</strong></p>

<p>Depending on your experience with cannabis, you may find that cannabis use for athletic performance is either controversial or &ndash; makes total sense. But the science is there, and more elite sports groups have already banned cannabis testing, with more expected to do so in the future.</p>

<p>Additionally, athletes can&rsquo;t deny the benefits. You don&rsquo;t even have to be a professional athlete to yield the benefits of cannabis for your workout. There are many ways it can benefit your regular workout, such as:</p>

<p><strong>Pain relief</strong>:<a href="https://cannabis.net/blog/medical/cannabis-strains-vs.-chronic-pain">&nbsp;Pain</a>&nbsp;is one of the most established conditions that cannabis can effectively and safely treat. Both THC and CBD have been found to be successful at treating inflammation, including inflammation caused by strenuous workouts and muscle soreness, which lead to pain.</p>

<p><strong>Stimulate your appetite</strong>: Weightlifters, boxers, or anyone who wants to build up mass and muscle can benefit from the&nbsp;<a href="https://cannabis.net/blog/medical/top-5-cannabis-strains-for-appetite-loss">appetite-inducing benefits</a>&nbsp;of marijuana. The THC content in certain cannabis strains and products is known for its infamous effect of inducing &ldquo;the munchies&rdquo;, but use it properly by eating the right foods necessary to meet your target weight in a healthy manner. THC acts on the brain&rsquo;s <a href="https://elplanteo.com/receptores-cb1/">CB1</a> receptors, which are also responsible for regulating appetite. You can hit two birds with one stone: benefit from the pain-relieving and relaxing properties of THC while also stimulating your appetite.</p>

<p>A word of caution, though: if you have asthma or other lung disorders, it&rsquo;s best to avoid smoking weed for exercise and/or recovery. Instead, opt to ingest weed in other forms that don&rsquo;t pass through your lungs. There are many choices for that these days, including edibles, oils, beverages, tinctures, and topicals. Invest time in experimenting on various products recommended by budtenders at licensed dispensaries to improve athletic performance. Some fitness enthusiasts prefer CBD only, while others prefer a low THC/high CBD ratio or high THC. The results will vary depending on your body and your own athletic needs.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Reimagine Your Cannabis Experience: Feel Good Without The Overwhelming High Of High-THC Weed</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/34097939/reimagine-your-cannabis-experience-feel-good-without-the-overwhelming-high-of-high-thc-weed</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/34097939/reimagine-your-cannabis-experience-feel-good-without-the-overwhelming-high-of-high-thc-weed</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:54:30 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>This article was originally published on <a href="https://thefreshtoast.com/cannabis/the-effects-of-smoking-low-thc-high-cbd-cannabis/">The Fresh Toast</a> and appears here with permission.</p>

<p>For decades, growers have been focused on producing cannabis strains with the highest THC content possible to have a maximum high. High-THC means you&rsquo;re getting baked, whether sativa, indica or a mix of the two. Now, however, we know CBD can be therapeutic, healing parts of the plant and growers are focusing on high-CBD cannabis that places <a href="https://elplanteo.com/que-es-el-thc/">THC</a> in the backseat. &nbsp;What are the effects of smoking low-THC, high-CBD cannabis? And what are the benefits?</p>

<p>While CBD doesn&rsquo;t get the patient high, it does provide a sense of well-being and calm. CBD from hemp is legal across the US, while CBD from cannabis is only legal in states that allow for medical and recreational usage. What about a combination?</p>

<p><em><strong>See also: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/biotech/21/10/17885544/far-more-potent-than-thc-and-cbd-dr-raphael-mechoulam">The &#39;Father Of Cannabis Research&#39; Discovered Something More Potent Than THC Before Dying: Here&#39;s What</a></strong></em></p>

<p>For one thing, there will be a change in mood, just not a drastic one that either has you talking a mile a minute or locked to the couch. The feeling is cerebral and one of well-being. The low-THC cannabis makes you feel comfortable in your own skin and has the healing benefits of whole-plant medication.</p>

<p>Data shows CBD can help you quit smoking cigarettes, and manage your diabetes, acne,&nbsp;<a href="https://crohnsandcolitis.ca/About-Crohn-s-Colitis/IBD-Journey/Treatment-and-Medications/Medical-Cannabis#:~:text=The%20use%20of%20cannabis%20for,reported%20improvement%20with%20smoked%20cannabis." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" title="Crohn's">Crohn&rsquo;s</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/315348#:~:text=Medical%20marijuana%20may%20be%20an,occur%20naturally%20in%20the%20body." rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" title="fibromyalgia">fibromyalgia</a>, multiple sclerosis, insomnia, and more. However, there must be more research to better understand the benefits and how the combination can enhance medical treatments.</p>

<p>So consuming low-THC, high-CBD bud is a little like smoking with the three bears. The high THC strain gets you really high, while the hemp CBD strain doesn&rsquo;t get you high at all. The strain that has a little THC and a lot of CBD? It&rsquo;s just right to have you feeling on cloud nine without altering your state to an extreme.</p>

<p><em><strong>See also: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/21/11/23825005/study-shows-cannabis-consumers-are-successful-motivated-health-conscious-snoop-dogg-weighs-in">Snoop Dogg Shatters Cannabis Clich&eacute;s: Consumers Are Highly Educated, Successful, Motivated</a></strong></em></p>

<p>And beyond being &ldquo;better than nothing,&rdquo; the high you get added to the relief you feel equals an experience that leaves a lasting impression and will likely have you going back to the bong. It&rsquo;s nearly impossible to get &ldquo;too high&rdquo; on low-THC cannabis, but you are able to find the bliss level.</p>

<p>So as growers expand their lines to include these new forms of medicinal marijuana, they are bound to continue improving upon the genetics, coaxing all the more <a href="https://elplanteo.com/cbd-gummies-mitos-verdades/">CBD</a> out and finding the most beneficial cannabinoids, terpenes and flavonoids to create the finest low-THC, high-CBD cannabis out there. Craft cannabis is definitely the new name of the game and this cannabinoid combo fits right in.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Punchbowl's Jake Sherman Posts "Kevin McCarthy Is Endorsing Tom Emmer For Speaker "He Is The Right Person For The Job. He Can Unite The Conference. He Understand The Dynamics Of The Conference. He Also Understands What It Takes To Win And Keep A Majority"</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35357611/punchbowls-jake-sherman-posts-kevin-mccarthy-is-endorsing-tom-emmer-for-speaker-h</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35357611/punchbowls-jake-sherman-posts-kevin-mccarthy-is-endorsing-tom-emmer-for-speaker-h</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:54:11 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://twitter.com/JakeSherman/status/1715455580054184375" title="https://twitter.com/JakeSherman/status/1715455580054184375">https://twitter.com/JakeSherman/status/1715455580054184375</a></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>A Brighter Future For Desperate Hemp Farmers? Cornell Research Could Make It Possible, Here's How</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35351454/a-brighter-future-for-desperate-hemp-farmers-cornell-research-could-make-it-possible-heres-how</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35351454/a-brighter-future-for-desperate-hemp-farmers-cornell-research-could-make-it-possible-heres-how</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:40:01 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>The Foundation for Food &amp; Agriculture Research</strong>&rsquo;s (FFAR)<strong> Hemp Research Consortium </strong>provided two grants totaling $1.17 million to Cornell University to support a long-term breeding program to cultivate hemp for grain, fiber and CBD production in U.S. growing regions. Consortium partners contributed matching funds for a total investment of $2.34 million.</p>

<h3>Why It Matters</h3>

<p>U.S.-grown hemp crops can yield additional plant protein, health and personal care products, consumer textiles and industrial applications.</p>

<p>Hemp may also be a viable alternative crop for tobacco-dependent and economically distressed farmers.</p>

<p>However, because Canada and Europe have longer days than the U.S. during the summer growing season, hemp varieties from these areas tend to result in smaller yields and thus limited profit when grown in the U.S. This is particularly true in sub-tropical regions such as Florida.</p>

<p>Cornell researchers aim to understand the genetic basis of the photoperiod threshold, which is the amount of light a plant needs to achieve flowering and other types of development.</p>

<p><em>See also: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/08/33661988/lack-of-oversight-continues-to-hurt-hemp-industry-what-to-expect-from-2023-farm-bill">Lack Of Oversight Continues To Hurt Hemp Industry, What To Expect From 2023 Farm Bill</a></em></p>

<h3>The Research</h3>

<p>The researchers are also<strong> </strong>developing varieties of hemp that will deliver higher yields, especially at lower latitudes in the U.S.</p>

<p>These plants are specifically bred for desired traits, using a marker-assisted selection that shows promise in southern latitudes and has specific desirable characteristics. Marker-assisted selection uses markers such as DNA linked to desired features to choose plants for breeding. Those new cultivars show improved grain and fiber yields and undetectable levels of THC, making them fully compliant with THC regulations.</p>

<p>&ldquo;With its potential for hundreds of food and industrial applications, hemp can be a major cash crop in the U.S<strong>.</strong>,&rdquo; <strong>Dr. Angela Records,</strong> FFAR chief scientific officer&nbsp;said. &ldquo;This research will contribute to a burgeoning hemp industry by acclimating the crop to a variety of growing regions across the country.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The research team is led by <strong>Dr. Larry Smart,</strong> a professor at Cornell&rsquo;s School of Integrative Plant Science Horticulture Section Plant Breeding and Genetics Section.</p>

<p><em>Now read:<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/05/32659550/legislative-developments-empower-hemp-farmers-boost-marijuana-sales-and-promote-equity-in"> Legislative Developments Empower Hemp Farmers, Boost Marijuana Sales And Promote Equity</a></em></p>

<p><em><strong>Missed the first wave of cannabis investments? Don&rsquo;t make that mistake again.</strong><br />
Experts believe <strong><a class="c-link" href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">cannabis stocks have found their floor</a></strong><strong> and are now poised for unprecedented growth.</strong> Join <strong><a class="c-link" href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Benzinga PotProfits</a></strong><strong>. </strong>Benefit from <a class="c-link" href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Michael Berger&rsquo;s sharp analysis</a>, revealing top cannabis stock opportunities and timely updates. Experience the potential of 10%+ returns in just 90 days. Our 4.5-star Marketfy rating speaks volumes. Secure your position in this booming sector with a <strong>30-day money-back guarantee.</strong> The time to invest is now, before everyone else realizes it. Secure your profits with Benzinga. <a class="c-link" href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Click here now to learn more</a>. </em></p>

<p><em>Photo: Courtesy of y <a href="https://unsplash.com/@matteopaga?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Matteo Paganelli</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/green-cannabis-plants-during-daytime-MqISkm2iLGc?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>FDA Approves PENBRAYA, The First And Only Vaccine For The Prevention Of The Five Most Common Serogroups Causing Meningococcal Disease In Adolescents</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/general/biotech/23/10/35357478/fda-approves-penbraya-the-first-and-only-vaccine-for-the-prevention-of-the-five-most-common-serog</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/general/biotech/23/10/35357478/fda-approves-penbraya-the-first-and-only-vaccine-for-the-prevention-of-the-five-most-common-serog</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:36:53 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<ul><li><i>PENBRAYA</i>&#x2122;<i> provides the broadest serogroup coverage (meningococcal groups A, B, C, W and Y) of any meningococcal vaccine available in the U.S. and has the potential to help simplify complex vaccination schedule in the U.S.</i></li><li><i>The FDA's decision is based on data from Phase 2 and Phase 3 trials, which demonstrated that PENBRAYA has robust immunogenicity non-inferior to Trumenba&#xAE; + Menveo&#xAE; for all serogroups and was well-tolerated with a favorable safety profile</i></li><li><i>The vaccine further advances Pfizer's vaccine portfolio and builds on more than 20 years of expertise and knowledge in the prevention of meningococcal disease</i></li></ul><p>Pfizer Inc. (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/PFE#NYSE">PFE</a>) announced today that the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) has approved PENBRAYA&#x2122; (meningococcal groups A, B, C, W and Y vaccine), the first and only pentavalent vaccine that provides coverage against the most common serogroups causing meningococcal disease in adolescents and young adults 10 through 25 years of age. PENBRAYA combines the components from two meningococcal vaccines, Trumenba&#xAE; (meningococcal group B vaccine) and Nimenrix&#xAE; (meningococcal groups A, C, W-135, and Y conjugate vaccine) to help protect against the five most common meningococcal serogroups that cause the majority of invasive meningococcal disease (IMD) globally.1</p><p>"As a pioneer in vaccines, one of our goals is to deliver vaccines that evolve the paradigm and help simplify the standard of care in the U.S.," said Annaliesa Anderson, Ph.D., Senior Vice President and Head, Vaccine Research and Development, Pfizer. "Today marks an important step forward in the prevention of meningococcal disease in the U.S. In a single vaccine, PENBRAYA has the potential to protect more adolescents and young adults from this severe and unpredictable disease by providing the broadest meningococcal coverage in the fewest shots."</p><p>Meningococcal disease is an uncommon but serious illness that can lead to death within 24 hours and, for survivors, can result in life-altering, significant long-term disabilities.2 PENBRAYA reduces the total number of doses needed for individuals to be fully vaccinated against the five most common serogroups, thereby streamlining the standard of care and potentially increasing the number of adolescents and young adults vaccinated.3 According to the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), combining vaccines into fewer shots may mean that more adolescents and young adults get their recommended vaccines on time, resulting in fewer delays in protection against serious diseases.4 Routine use of PENBRAYA could also reduce IMD cases and associated mortality, the rate of long-term consequences of infection (sequelae) in survivors and costs associated with controlling outbreaks.5</p><p>"Nearly 9 out of 10 adolescents have incomplete protection against invasive meningococcal disease caused by the leading serogroups6," said Jana Shaw, MD, Pediatrics Infectious Disease Specialist, Upstate Golisano Children's Hospital in Syracuse, NY. "For the first time, we have a single vaccine that helps protect against the five most common serogroups and has the potential to improve coverage and increase protection among adolescents and young adults."</p><p>The FDA's decision is based on the positive results from the Phase 2 and Phase 3 trials, including a randomized, active-controlled and observer-blinded Phase 3 trial assessing the safety, tolerability, and immunogenicity of the pentavalent vaccine candidate compared to currently U.S. licensed meningococcal vaccines, with the goal of determining immunologic noninferiority. The Phase 3 trial <a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fclassic.clinicaltrials.gov%2Fct2%2Fshow%2FNCT04440163&amp;esheet=53639237&amp;newsitemid=20231019164717&amp;lan=en-US&amp;anchor=%28NCT04440163%29&amp;index=1&amp;md5=598bbe9f5389df3c5131012698727c0a">(NCT04440163)</a> evaluated more than 2,400 patients from the U.S. and Europe.</p><p>The CDC Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) will meet on October 25, 2023, to discuss recommendations for the appropriate use of PENBRAYA in adolescents and young adults.</p><p><strong>About PENBRAYA Regulatory Review</strong></p><p>In September 2022, Pfizer <a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.pfizer.com%2Fnews%2Fpress-release%2Fpress-release-detail%2Fpfizer-announces-positive-top-line-results-phase-3-trial-0&amp;esheet=53639237&amp;newsitemid=20231019164717&amp;lan=en-US&amp;anchor=announced&amp;index=2&amp;md5=f3b40b65b4ac51d2594f1ec2d91958b1">announced</a> positive results from a randomized, active-controlled and observer-blinded Phase 3 trial assessing the safety, tolerability, and immunogenicity of the PENBRAYA compared to currently licensed meningococcal vaccines, with the goal of determining immunologic noninferiority. The Phase 3 trial (NCT04440163) evaluated more than 2,400 patients from the U.S. and Europe. This trial was followed by the FDA's <a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.pfizer.com%2Fnews%2Fpress-release%2Fpress-release-detail%2Fus-fda-accepts-review-biologics-license-application-pfizers&amp;esheet=53639237&amp;newsitemid=20231019164717&amp;lan=en-US&amp;anchor=acceptance&amp;index=3&amp;md5=73454d9e4990ddda72a8cf1959c1f15a">acceptance</a> of PENBRAYA's Biologics License Application (BLA) in December 2022.</p><p><strong>Indication for PENBRAYA</strong></p><p>PENBRAYA is indicated for active immunization to prevent invasive disease caused by <i>Neisseria meningitidis</i> serogroups A, B, C, W, and Y. PENBRAYA is approved for use in individuals 10 through 25 years of age.</p><p>PENBRAYA is administered as a two-dose series given six months apart.</p><p><strong>Important Safety Information for PENBRAYA</strong></p><ul><li>PENBRAYA should not be given to anyone with a history of a severe allergic reaction to any component of PENBRAYA</li><li>Fainting may happen after getting injectable vaccines, including PENBRAYA. Precautions should be taken to avoid falling and injury due to fainting</li><li>Some individuals with weakened immune system may have reduced immune responses to PENBRAYA</li><li>Individuals with certain complement deficiencies and individuals receiving treatment that inhibits terminal complement activation are at increased risk for invasive disease caused by <i>N. meningitidis</i> groups A, B, C, W, and Y, even if they develop antibodies following vaccination with PENBRAYA</li><li>Vaccination with PENBRAYA may not protect all who receive the vaccine against&nbsp;<i>N. meningitidis</i>&nbsp;group A, B, C, W, and Y infections</li><li>Vaccination with PENBRAYA does not substitute for vaccination with a tetanus toxoidcontaining vaccine to prevent tetanus</li><li>Guillain-Barr syndrome (GBS) has been reported following administration of other meningococcal vaccines. Ask your healthcare provider about the risks and benefits of PENBRAYA if you have a history of GBS</li><li>The most common adverse reactions were pain at the injection site, fatigue, headache, injection site redness, muscle pain, injection site swelling, joint pain, and chills.</li><li>Tell your healthcare provider if you are pregnant or plan to become pregnant</li><li>Ask your healthcare provider about the risks and benefits of PENBRAYA. Only a healthcare provider can decide if PENBRAYA is right for you or your child</li></ul><p><a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Flabeling.pfizer.com%2FShowLabeling.aspx%3Fid%3D19937&amp;esheet=53639237&amp;newsitemid=20231019164717&amp;lan=en-US&amp;anchor=View+the+full+Prescribing+Information.&amp;index=4&amp;md5=7a97323f5fc87a797ec036e64f7c0879">View the full Prescribing Information.</a> There may be a delay as the document is updated with the latest information. It will be available as soon as possible. Please check back for the updated full information shortly.</p><p><strong>U.S. Indication for TRUMENBA</strong>&#xAE;<strong> (meningococcal group B vaccine)</strong></p><p>TRUMENBA&#xAE; (meningococcal group B vaccine) is indicated for active immunization to prevent invasive disease caused by <i>Neisseria meningitidis</i> serogroup B in individuals aged 10 through 25 years of age. Approval of TRUMENBA&#xAE; is based on the demonstration of immune response, as measured by serum bactericidal activity against four serogroup B strains representative of prevalent strains in the United States. The effectiveness of TRUMENBA&#xAE; against diverse serogroup B strains has not been confirmed.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Feutune Light Acquisition Corporation Announces Extension Of The Deadline For An Initial Business Combination To November 21, 2023</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/m-a/23/10/35357418/feutune-light-acquisition-corporation-announces-extension-of-the-deadline-for-an-initial-business-co</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/m-a/23/10/35357418/feutune-light-acquisition-corporation-announces-extension-of-the-deadline-for-an-initial-business-co</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:35:24 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Feutune Light Acquisition Corporation (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/FLFV#NASDAQ">FLFV</a>) (the "Company"), a blank check company incorporated as a Delaware corporation, today announced that, in order to extend the date by which the Company must complete its initial business combination from October 21, 2023 to November 21, 2023, an aggregate of $100,000 has been deposited into Company's trust account (the "Trust Account").</p><p>Pursuant to the Company's Amended and Restated Certificate of Incorporation currently in effect, the Company may extend on monthly basis from June 21, 2023 until March 21, 2024 or such an earlier date as may be determined by its board to complete a business combination by depositing $100,000 for each month into the Trust Account.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>White House Says Biden, Israel PM Discussed Efforts To Secure Release Of Hostages Taken By Hamas And To Provide For Safe Passage For Civilians In Gaza</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35357400/white-house-says-biden-israel-pm-discussed-efforts-to-secure-release-of-hostages-</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35357400/white-house-says-biden-israel-pm-discussed-efforts-to-secure-release-of-hostages-</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:34:03 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/10/20/readout-of-president-bidens-call-with-prime-minister-netanyahu-of-israel-4/" title="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/10/20/readout-of-president-bidens-call-with-prime-minister-netanyahu-of-israel-4/">https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/10/20/readout-of-president-bidens-call-with-prime-minister-netanyahu-of-israel-4/</a></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hamas Releases 2 American Hostages Amid Escalating Tensions: Calls For Ceasefire Grow</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/etfs/broad-u-s-equity-etfs/23/10/35357397/hamas-releases-2-american-hostages-amid-escalating-tensions-calls-for-ceasefire-grow</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/etfs/broad-u-s-equity-etfs/23/10/35357397/hamas-releases-2-american-hostages-amid-escalating-tensions-calls-for-ceasefire-grow</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:33:43 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Two American hostages, <strong>Judith Raanan</strong> and her daughter <strong>Natalie</strong>, 18, were released by Hamas on Friday afternoon and subsequently transferred into the custody of the Red Cross, according to the Israeli government.They are reportedly <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/topic/israel">under the care Israeli authorities. </a></p>



<p>Raanan and her daughter are from Evanston, Illinois, a suburb of Chicago, and they had embarked on a trip to Israel earlier this month to partake in the festivities surrounding a relative&#8217;s 85th birthday and the Jewish holiday season. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Two of the hostages, mother and daughter Yehudit Tai and Natali Shoshana Raanan were released by the Hamas terror organization and were transferred to the Israeli border via the Red Cross.<br><br>They are on their way to an army base in central Israel were their families are anxiously <a href="https://t.co/xCGFfVEQa1">pic.twitter.com/xCGFfVEQa1</a></p>&mdash; Israel  &#x1f1ee;&#x1f1f1; (@Israel) <a href="https://twitter.com/Israel/status/1715439615962702145?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 20, 2023</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p><strong>Ghazi Hamad</strong>, a Hamas political bureau member, called the release a goodwill gesture during an exclusive interview with <a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/liveblog/2023/10/19/israel-hamas-war-live-condemnation-after-israeli-strike-on-gaza-church">Al Jazeera</a>. Hamas is ready for constructive talks about prisoners, he said, but insisted that Israeli airstrikes in Gaza must stop. Hamas is treating the captives with dignity and respect, Hamad said, adding the release was facilitated through Qatari mediation. </p>



<p>Conversely, CNN reports that Hamas released the Americans due to the mother&#8217;s declining health, while the Times of Israel suggested the United States had also played a role in these efforts.</p>



<p>The U.S. and European governments are pushing Israel to delay its Gaza ground invasion to give diplomacy an opportunity to free other hostages held by Hamas.</p>



<p>The Israeli military has ordered for the immediate evacuation of Al-Quds Hospital in Gaza City, calling upon all occupants to relocate to the southern region. Presently, the hospital is catering to the needs of 400 patients and roughly 12,000 displaced civilians.</p>



<p>Lebanese Foreign Minister <strong>Abdallah Bou Habib</strong> is urging Israel to announce a 48-hour ceasefire. According to Israel Defense Forces spokesperson Lt. Col. <strong>Peter Lerner </strong>in his conversation with <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/israel-hamas-war-gaza-news-10-20-23/index.html">CNN</a>, it is the Lebanese government&#8217;s responsibility to ensure that terrorist groups like Hezbollah refrain from launching attacks against Israel.</p>



<p>President<strong> Joe Biden </strong>has said the Rafah crossing between Gaza and Egypt should be ready to reopen within the next 24-48 hours to facilitate the entry of humanitarian aid into Gaza.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Market Reactions</h2>



<p>During the entire trading session on Friday in New York, stocks remained consistently under pressure. </p>



<p>The S&amp;P 500 Index, as tracked by the <strong>SPDR S&amp;P 500 ETF Trust</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/SPY#NYSE">SPY</a>), recorded a 0.9% decline, while the tech-focused <strong>Invesco QQQ Trust</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/QQQ#NASDAQ">QQQ</a>) saw a 1.1% decrease.</p>



<p>Investors opted for safer assets, resulting in gains for both Treasuries and gold. The <strong>iShares 20+ Year Treasury ETF</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TLT#NASDAQ">TLT</a>) rose by 0.6%, and the <strong>SPDR Gold Trust </strong>(NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/GLD#NYSE">GLD</a>) showed a 0.4% increase.</p>



<p>Read now: <em><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35347388/nasdaq-s-p-500-futures-sag-on-rate-worries-mixed-earnings-analyst-touts-2-data-points-for-possible-">Stocks Suffer, Safe Havens Rise As Investors Fear Escalation In Middle East: What&#8217;s Driving Markets Friday?</a></em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>White House Says Biden Spoke Friday With Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu Of Israel; Biden, Israel PM Discussed Follow-Up From President's Visit To Israel, Including Plans To Begin Moving Humanitarian Assistance Into Gaza From Egypt</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35357382/white-house-says-biden-spoke-friday-with-prime-minister-benjamin-netanyahu-of-isr</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35357382/white-house-says-biden-spoke-friday-with-prime-minister-benjamin-netanyahu-of-isr</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:32:18 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/10/20/readout-of-president-bidens-call-with-prime-minister-netanyahu-of-israel-4/" title="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/10/20/readout-of-president-bidens-call-with-prime-minister-netanyahu-of-israel-4/">https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/10/20/readout-of-president-bidens-call-with-prime-minister-netanyahu-of-israel-4/</a></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Orange Photonics: New High-Tech Testing For Psychedelic Products</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35356500/orange-photonics-new-high-tech-testing-for-psychedelic-products</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35356500/orange-photonics-new-high-tech-testing-for-psychedelic-products</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:32:18 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Orange Photonics</strong> has launched <strong>LightLab 3 Psy Analyzer</strong> for the measurement of <strong>psilocybin, psilocin and 5-AcO-DMT </strong>in psychedelic mushrooms, extracts and infused products.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Using High Performance Liquid Chromatography (HPLC),&nbsp;&rdquo;the same tech favored by nearly all testing labs,&rdquo;&nbsp;the new tool aims to support data-driven decisions on strain selection, harvest optimization, extraction, accurate dosing, and safety.</p>

<p>Designed for licensed operators and research institutions and yet reportedly holding a portable, non-technical user type, LightLab was initially developed for cannabis testing applications and now aims to play a pivotal&nbsp;role in cultivation, production and regulatory applications for psychedelics.</p>

<p><em>See Also: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/06/32788090/ai-powered-psychedelic-treatments-special-status-and-next-gen-contests-winners">AI-Powered Psychedelic Treatments: Special Status And Next-Gen Contests Winners</a></em></p>

<p>Orange Photonics aims to provide accurate, reliable and innovative analytical testing solutions for several industries. Since 2015, LighLab 3 technology has been used by cannabis operators as well as state and federal regulators,&nbsp;reportedly including&nbsp;the FDA ,&nbsp;universities and research institutions.</p>

<p>Orange&rsquo;s president<strong> Stephanie McArdle</strong> says LightLab represents the opportunity to incorporate on-site potency analysis into every element of manufacturing and regulation.</p>

<p>&quot;Psychedelics product producers are in a position to ensure consumer safety is a primary focus. LightLab 3 Psy Analyzer is optimized for that critical role,&quot; McArdle stated.</p>

<p><em><strong>Missed the first wave of cannabis investments? Don&rsquo;t make that mistake again.</strong><br />
Experts believe&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">cannabis stocks have found their floor</a></strong><strong>&nbsp;and are now poised for unprecedented growth.</strong>&nbsp;Join&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Benzinga PotProfits</a></strong><strong>.&nbsp;</strong>Benefit from&nbsp;<a href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Michael Berger&rsquo;s sharp analysis</a>, revealing top cannabis stock opportunities and timely updates. Experience the potential of 10%+ returns in just 90 days. Our 4.5-star Marketfy rating speaks volumes. Secure your position in this booming sector with a&nbsp;<strong>30-day money-back guarantee.</strong>&nbsp;The time to invest is now, before everyone else realizes it. Secure your profits with Benzinga.</em>&nbsp;<a href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Click here now to learn more</a>.</p>

<p><em>Photo cortesy of&nbsp;<a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/shallow-focus-photography-of-white-bottle-lot-HMQtSQZHPZU?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Paramount Cancels 2023 MTV Europe Music Awards Amid Israel-Gaza Conflict</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/asia/23/10/35356170/paramount-cancels-2023-mtv-europe-music-awards-amid-israel-gaza-conflict</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/asia/23/10/35356170/paramount-cancels-2023-mtv-europe-music-awards-amid-israel-gaza-conflict</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:31:57 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Paramount Global</strong> (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/PARAA#NASDAQ">PARAA</a>)(NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/PARA#NASDAQ">PARA</a>) canceled the<strong> 2023 MTV Europe Music Awards</strong> (EMAs) scheduled for Nov.&nbsp;5 in Paris, attributing the decision to the <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/global/23/10/35350197/israel-hamas-war-day-14-biden-highlights-historic-crossroads-idf-strikes-intensify-aid-delivery-to-g">&quot;volatility of world events.&quot;</a></p>

<p>The cancellation came&nbsp;as the conflict in the Middle East, particularly the Israel-Gaza war, intensified, Deadline <a href="https://deadline.com/2023/10/paramount-cancels-2023-mtv-emas-in-paris-israel-gaza-crisis-1235578010/">reported.</a></p>

<p><em>See Also:<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/asia/23/10/35339969/israeli-army-gets-green-light-to-move-into-gaza-netanyahu-says-warriors-are-ready-us-issues-global-t">&nbsp;Israeli Army Gets &#39;Green Light&#39; To Move Into Gaza: Netanyahu Says &#39;Warriors Are Ready,&#39; US Issues Global Travel Warning</a></em></p>

<p>France is on high alert following the recent murder of a schoolteacher in the wake of a Hamas-led attack on Israel. Several airports, including Nice, were temporarily evacuated due to security threats.</p>

<p>Paramount cited concerns for the safety of thousands of employees, crew members, artists, fans&nbsp;and partners who come from around the world to participate in the event.</p>

<p>&quot;The MTV EMAs are an annual celebration of global music. As we watch the devastating events in Israel and Gaza continue to unfold, this does not feel like a moment for a global celebration. With thousands of lives already lost, it is a moment of mourning,&quot; a Paramount spokesperson said.</p>

<p>Paramount expressed hope to host the MTV EMAs again in November 2024, prioritizing the safety and well-being of all involved, acknowledging that the current global situation is not conducive to a celebratory event.</p>

<p>This cancellation follows a trend of postponements and cancellations of events due to the Israel-Gaza crisis.</p>

<p><em>Read Next:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/entertainment/23/08/33927835/this-is-the-secret-for-a-viral-music-video-according-to-the-powerhouse-behind-latin-traps-c">This Is The Secret For A Viral Music Video, According To The Powerhouse Behind Latin Trap&#39;s Chart-Topping Productions</a></em></p>

<p><em>Photo: Concert photo,&nbsp;<a href="https://unsplash.com/@tijsvl?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Tijs van Leur</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/people-raising-their-hands-on-concert-Qnlp3FCO2vc?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Here's How Much You Would Have Made Owning Prologis Stock In The Last 15 Years</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357360/heres-how-much-you-would-have-made-owning-prologis-stock-in-the-last-15-years</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357360/heres-how-much-you-would-have-made-owning-prologis-stock-in-the-last-15-years</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:30:36 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Prologis (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/PLD#NYSE">PLD</a>) has outperformed the market over the past 15 years by 2.19% on an annualized basis producing an average annual return of 13.56%. Currently, Prologis has a market capitalization of $95.34 billion. </p>
<p><strong>Buying $1000 In PLD:</strong> If an investor had bought $1000 of PLD stock 15 years ago, it would be worth <strong>$5,762.14</strong> today based on a price of $103.20 for PLD at the time of writing.</p>
<h3>Prologis's Performance Over Last 15 Years</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697830233_0.png" alt="comp_fig" /></p>

<p>Finally -- what's the point of all this? The key insight to take from this article is to note how much of a difference compounded returns can make in your cash growth over a period of time.</p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>$100 Invested In Elevance Health 10 Years Ago Would Be Worth This Much Today</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357357/100-invested-in-elevance-health-10-years-ago-would-be-worth-this-much-today</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357357/100-invested-in-elevance-health-10-years-ago-would-be-worth-this-much-today</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:30:31 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Elevance Health (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/ELV#NYSE">ELV</a>) has outperformed the market over the past 10 years by 9.25% on an annualized basis producing an average annual return of 18.45%. Currently, Elevance Health has a market capitalization of $107.11 billion. </p>
<p><strong>Buying $100 In ELV:</strong> If an investor had bought $100 of ELV stock 10 years ago, it would be worth <strong>$531.76</strong> today based on a price of $454.55 for ELV at the time of writing.</p>
<h3>Elevance Health's Performance Over Last 10 Years</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697830228_0.png" alt="comp_fig" /></p>

<p>Finally -- what's the point of all this? The key insight to take from this article is to note how much of a difference compounded returns can make in your cash growth over a period of time.</p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Oppenheimer Maintains Outperform on Blackstone, Lowers Price Target to $105</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357308/oppenheimer-maintains-outperform-on-blackstone-lowers-price-target-to-105</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357308/oppenheimer-maintains-outperform-on-blackstone-lowers-price-target-to-105</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:23:51 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Oppenheimer  analyst Chris Kotowski   maintains Blackstone (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/BX#NYSE">BX</a>) with a Outperform and lowers the price target from $107 to $105.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Oppenheimer Maintains Outperform on Pool, Lowers Price Target to $370</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357288/oppenheimer-maintains-outperform-on-pool-lowers-price-target-to-370</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357288/oppenheimer-maintains-outperform-on-pool-lowers-price-target-to-370</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:21:26 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Oppenheimer  analyst Scott Schneeberger   maintains Pool (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/POOL#NASDAQ">POOL</a>) with a Outperform and lowers the price target from $375 to $370.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Oppenheimer Maintains Outperform on Amgen, Raises Price Target to $300</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357246/oppenheimer-maintains-outperform-on-amgen-raises-price-target-to-300</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357246/oppenheimer-maintains-outperform-on-amgen-raises-price-target-to-300</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:19:27 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Oppenheimer  analyst Jay Olson   maintains Amgen (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/AMGN#NASDAQ">AMGN</a>) with a Outperform and raises the price target from $290 to $300.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Europe's High: Irish GPs Against Pot, Switzerland-Spain Share Data On Cannabis Clubs &amp; More</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35346758/europes-high-irish-gps-against-pot-switzerland-spain-share-data-on-cannabis-clubs-more</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35346758/europes-high-irish-gps-against-pot-switzerland-spain-share-data-on-cannabis-clubs-more</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:19:14 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<h3><strong>Denmark: Medical Marijuana Pilot Program Experience 90% Growth In 12 Months </strong></h3>

<p>The number of patients enrolled in Denmark&rsquo;s medical cannabis pilot trial grew more than 90% in 12 months,&nbsp;<a href="https://businessofcannabis.com/denmarks-medical-cannabis-pilot-programme-has-seen-90-growth-over-the-last-year/" target="_blank">writes</a>&nbsp;Business of Cannabis.</p>

<p>According to the report from the Danish Health Data Authority, the number of patients involved in the medical marijuana Pilot Programme, which commenced in 2018, hit record numbers in 2023. Now, it makes for the biggest access scheme in the country.</p>

<p>With medical marijuana not being completely regulated in Denmark there are various access schemes, such as:</p>

<ul>
	<li>
	<p><strong>Magistral Scheme</strong>&nbsp;&ndash; under which patients can access only products with CBD and THC isolates, so do not contain the cannabinoids present in full spectrum oils;</p>
	</li>
	<li>
	<p><strong>&nbsp;Pilot Programme</strong>&nbsp;- allows all doctors to prescribe any of the unlicensed medicines that have been approved for trial for any condition;&nbsp;</p>
	</li>
	<li>
	<p><strong>Pharmaceutical Scheme</strong>, which only allows&nbsp;<strong>Jazz Pharmaceuticals&#39;</strong>&nbsp;(NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/JAZZ#NASDAQ">JAZZ</a>) Sativex and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/topic/epidiolex" target="_blank">Epidoloex</a>.&nbsp;</p>
	</li>
</ul>

<p>The popularity rise of the Pilot scheme could be attributed to several reasons among which are: the ability for any doctor to prescribe, the products based on the full spectrum cannabis plant, said&nbsp;<strong>Thomas Skovlund Schnegelsberg</strong>, CEO of Danish medical cannabis operator&nbsp;<strong>Stenocare</strong>.</p>

<p>&ldquo;This means you don&rsquo;t get the entourage effect that, according to the doctors that I&rsquo;ve talked to&hellip; say they see a higher efficacy with the full spectrum, with all the cannabinoids,&rdquo; Schnegelsberg said. He also added that the number revealed a preference shift to oils from flower.&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>Malta: Government Employee-Led Cannabis Club Breaks&nbsp;Advertising Rules&nbsp;</strong></h3>

<p>One of the first provisionally licensed &ldquo;cannabis clubs&rdquo; in Malta, Sprawt Chra, seems to have violated the rules on advertising with its recent Facebook post,&nbsp;which was deleted,&nbsp;<a href="https://theshiftnews.com/2023/10/19/government-employee-cannabis-club-licensee-deletes-facebook-page-after-possible-rules-breach/" target="_blank">writes</a>&nbsp;the Shift.</p>

<p>Under Malta&rsquo;s cannabis law, only &ldquo;cannabis harm reduction associations&rdquo; are licensed and regulated to grow and sell cannabis. These associations must be non-profit, can only sell their product&nbsp;and are not allowed to advertise, put cannabis in the name&nbsp;or promote marijuana use in any way.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Based in ebbu, Sprawt,&nbsp;one of two associations to obtain an &ldquo;in-principle&rdquo; license, which means it was allowed to start the construction of cultivation facilities, but not to grow plants until it is granted a full permit. Sprawt is managed by a government employee as its key officer and treasurer is <strong>Andrew Cassar Overend</strong> who works at the National Development and Social Fund and was previously an economics officer in the Ministry of Finance and Employment.&nbsp;</p>

<p>In the controversial post, Sprawt invited people to embark on a &ldquo;weed-loving journey&rdquo; with &ldquo;sizzling events, blazing giveaways, and pot-tastic surprises.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The post and the entire Sprawt Facebook page have been deleted most likely due to the violation of advertising rules.&nbsp;</p>

<h3><strong>Ireland: College Of General Practitioners Warns About Cannabis Use&nbsp;</strong></h3>

<p>Irish College of General Practitioners (ICGP)&nbsp;<a href="https://www.icgp.ie/speck/properties/asset/asset.cfm?type=Document&amp;id=36DA4388-E0B0-4B09-BF7878E6FF5E8C0B&amp;property=document&amp;filename=ICGP_Statement_on_Cannabis.pdf&amp;revision=tip&amp;mimetype=application%2Fpdf&amp;app=icgp&amp;disposition=inline" target="_blank">issued a new statement</a>&nbsp;on cannabis use, strongly opposing possible legalization in the country.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Cannabis is a dangerous drug and a serious public health concern,&rdquo; reads the document issued by <strong>Dr. Diarmuid Quinlan</strong>, the ICGP&rsquo;s medical director. The ICGP discourages cannabis use, especially in high-risk populations such as youth, those with a personal or family history of mental disorder, pregnant women, and women who are breastfeeding,&rdquo;</p>

<p>The statement comes ahead of the final meeting of the Citizens&rsquo; Assembly on Drugs Use, which is scheduled for this weekend,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.irishexaminer.com/news/arid-41251747.html" target="_blank">writes</a>&nbsp;the Irish Examiner. The assembly is supposed to put together a report for the Oireachtas on recommendations to reduce harm caused by illegal drugs.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The ICGP also confirmed that there&rsquo;s evidence suggesting cannabis offers potential therapeutic benefits, it adds that there are &ldquo;notable public health and health impacts associated with its use.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>That&rsquo;s why it &ldquo;encourages the HSE and Department of Health to improve surveillance efforts to ensure data is available on the short- and long-term health effects of cannabis, especially emergency department visits and hospitalizations, impaired driving, workplace impairment and worker-related injury and safety, and prevalence of psychiatric and addictive disorders, including cannabis use disorder.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The IGCP noted it is behind public-health-based strategies, rather than incarcerations (in relation to individuals owning small amounts of marijuana for personal use), and is inviting for further research into the safety and effectiveness of cannabinoid-based medicinal products.</p>

<h3><strong>Switzerland: Explores Barcelona&#39;s Cannabis Social Club Model&nbsp;</strong></h3>

<p>In October, a group of Swiss public health professionals involved in the Zurich pilot cannabis program visited a local cannabis social club in Barcelona,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.iceers.org/swiss-professionals-explore-barcelonas-cannabis-social-club-model/" target="_blank">writes</a>&nbsp;Iceers. The idea behind the visit was to compare the programs and exchange experiences on harm reduction strategies.</p>

<p><em><strong>Did you miss the first wave of cannabis investments? Don&rsquo;t make that mistake again.</strong><br />
Experts believe <a href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" target="_blank"><strong>cannabis stocks have found their floor</strong></a> <strong>and are now poised for unprecedented growth.</strong> Join <strong><a href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" target="_blank">Benzinga PotProfits</a>. </strong>Benefit from <a href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" target="_blank">Michael Berger&rsquo;s sharp analysis</a>, revealing top cannabis stock opportunities and timely updates. Experience the potential of 10%+ returns in just 90 days. Our 4.5-star Marketfy rating speaks volumes. Secure your position in this booming sector with a <strong>30-day money-back guarantee.</strong> The time to invest is now&nbsp;before everyone else realizes it. Secure your profits with Benzinga. <a href="https://marketfy.com/item/420investor/" target="_blank">Click here now to learn more</a>.</em></p>

<p><em class="core-block">Photo: Benzinga edit with images by&nbsp;<a class="core-block" href="https://unsplash.com/@purzlbaum" target="_blank">Claudio Schwarz</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a class="core-block" href="https://unsplash.com/@briannjoness" target="_blank">Brian Jones</a>&nbsp;on Unsplash&nbsp;</em></p>

<p><br />
&nbsp;</p>

<p><br />
&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Newmont Unusual Options Activity</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/options/23/10/35357205/newmont-unusual-options-activity</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/options/23/10/35357205/newmont-unusual-options-activity</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:15:59 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Someone with a lot of money to spend has taken a bullish stance on <strong>Newmont</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/NEM#NYSE">NEM</a>).</p>
<p>And retail traders should know.</p>
<p>We noticed this today when the big position showed up on publicly available options history that we track here at Benzinga.</p>
<p>Whether this is an institution or just a wealthy individual, we don't know. But when something this big happens with NEM, it often means somebody knows something is about to happen.</p>
<p>So how do we know what this whale just did? </p>
<p>Today, <a href="https://pro.benzinga.com/?utm_source=insights">Benzinga</a>'s options scanner spotted 14 uncommon options trades for Newmont.</p>
<p>This isn't normal.</p>
<p>The overall sentiment of these big-money traders is split between 57% bullish and 42%, bearish.</p>
<p>Out of all of the special options we uncovered, 5 are puts, for a total amount of $224,678, and 9 are calls, for a total amount of $646,825.</p>
<h3>What's The Price Target?</h3>
<p>Taking into account the Volume and Open Interest on these contracts, it appears that whales have been targeting a price range from $30.0 to $45.0 for Newmont over the last 3 months. </p>
<h3>Volume &amp; Open Interest Development</h3>
<p>In terms of liquidity and interest, the mean open interest for Newmont options trades today is 4368.3 with a total volume of 17,840.00.</p>
<p>In the following chart, we are able to follow the development of volume and open interest of call and put options for Newmont's big money trades within a strike price range of $30.0 to $45.0 over the last 30 days.</p>
<h3>Newmont Option Volume And Open Interest Over Last 30 Days</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697829355_0.png" alt="Options Call Chart" /></p>

<h3>Biggest Options Spotted:</h3>
<p><table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th><strong>Symbol</strong></th>
<th><strong>PUT/CALL</strong></th>
<th><strong>Trade Type</strong></th>
<th><strong>Sentiment</strong></th>
<th><strong>Exp. Date</strong></th>
<th><strong>Strike Price</strong></th>
<th><strong>Total Trade Price</strong></th>
<th><strong>Open Interest</strong></th>
<th><strong>Volume</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>NEM</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>TRADE</td>
<td>BULLISH</td>
<td>01/19/24</td>
<td>$42.50</td>
<td>$266.0K</td>
<td>5.0K</td>
<td>2.0K</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>NEM</td>
<td>PUT</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BULLISH</td>
<td>11/17/23</td>
<td>$37.50</td>
<td>$74.2K</td>
<td>10.2K</td>
<td>1.0K</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>NEM</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BULLISH</td>
<td>01/19/24</td>
<td>$37.50</td>
<td>$69.1K</td>
<td>2.7K</td>
<td>1</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>NEM</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BEARISH</td>
<td>11/17/23</td>
<td>$37.50</td>
<td>$61.9K</td>
<td>2.7K</td>
<td>250</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>NEM</td>
<td>PUT</td>
<td>TRADE</td>
<td>BULLISH</td>
<td>11/17/23</td>
<td>$40.00</td>
<td>$58.6K</td>
<td>5.9K</td>
<td>1.9K</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table></p>
<h3>Where Is Newmont Standing Right Now?</h3>
<ul>
<li>With a volume of 11,856,933, the price of NEM is down -0.48% at $39.26. </li>
<li>RSI indicators hint that the underlying stock is currently neutral between overbought and oversold.</li>
<li>Next earnings are expected to be released in 6 days.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What The Experts Say On Newmont:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Jefferies has decided to maintain their Hold rating on Newmont, which currently sits at a price target of $38. </li>
</ul>
<p>Options are a riskier asset compared to just trading the stock, but they have higher profit potential. Serious options traders manage this risk by educating themselves daily, scaling in and out of trades, following more than one indicator, and following the markets closely.</p>
<p>If you want to stay updated on the latest options trades for Newmont, <a href="https://benzinga.grsm.io/register174">Benzinga Pro</a> gives you real-time options trades alerts.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Check Out What Whales Are Doing With URI</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/options/23/10/35357204/check-out-what-whales-are-doing-with-uri</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/options/23/10/35357204/check-out-what-whales-are-doing-with-uri</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:15:53 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Someone with a lot of money to spend has taken a bearish stance on <strong>United Rentals</strong> (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/URI#NYSE">URI</a>).</p>
<p>And retail traders should know.</p>
<p>We noticed this today when the big position showed up on publicly available options history that we track here at Benzinga.</p>
<p>Whether this is an institution or just a wealthy individual, we don't know. But when something this big happens with URI, it often means somebody knows something is about to happen.</p>
<p>So how do we know what this whale just did? </p>
<p>Today, <a href="https://pro.benzinga.com/?utm_source=insights">Benzinga</a>'s options scanner spotted 18 uncommon options trades for United Rentals.</p>
<p>This isn't normal.</p>
<p>The overall sentiment of these big-money traders is split between 27% bullish and 72%, bearish.</p>
<p>Out of all of the special options we uncovered, 5 are puts, for a total amount of $221,569, and 13 are calls, for a total amount of $1,654,601.</p>
<h3>What's The Price Target?</h3>
<p>Taking into account the Volume and Open Interest on these contracts, it appears that whales have been targeting a price range from $390.0 to $660.0 for United Rentals over the last 3 months. </p>
<h3>Volume &amp; Open Interest Development</h3>
<p>In terms of liquidity and interest, the mean open interest for United Rentals options trades today is 198.0 with a total volume of 1,843.00.</p>
<p>In the following chart, we are able to follow the development of volume and open interest of call and put options for United Rentals's big money trades within a strike price range of $390.0 to $660.0 over the last 30 days.</p>
<h3>United Rentals Option Volume And Open Interest Over Last 30 Days</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697829350_0.png" alt="Options Call Chart" /></p>

<h3>Biggest Options Spotted:</h3>
<p><table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th><strong>Symbol</strong></th>
<th><strong>PUT/CALL</strong></th>
<th><strong>Trade Type</strong></th>
<th><strong>Sentiment</strong></th>
<th><strong>Exp. Date</strong></th>
<th><strong>Strike Price</strong></th>
<th><strong>Total Trade Price</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Open Interest</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Volume</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>URI</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BEARISH</td>
<td>11/10/23</td>
<td>$390.00</td>
<td>$306.0K</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">107</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>URI</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BEARISH</td>
<td>11/10/23</td>
<td>$390.00</td>
<td>$300.0K</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">217</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>URI</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BEARISH</td>
<td>11/10/23</td>
<td>$390.00</td>
<td>$284.2K</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">370</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>URI</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BEARISH</td>
<td>01/17/25</td>
<td>$600.00</td>
<td>$185.9K</td>
<td align="right">412</td>
<td align="right">71</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>URI</td>
<td>CALL</td>
<td>SWEEP</td>
<td>BEARISH</td>
<td>11/10/23</td>
<td>$390.00</td>
<td>$165.0K</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">272</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table></p>
<h3>Where Is United Rentals Standing Right Now?</h3>
<ul>
<li>With a volume of 607,135, the price of URI is down 0.0% at $411.19. </li>
<li>RSI indicators hint that the underlying stock may be approaching oversold.</li>
<li>Next earnings are expected to be released in 5 days.</li>
</ul>
<p>Options are a riskier asset compared to just trading the stock, but they have higher profit potential. Serious options traders manage this risk by educating themselves daily, scaling in and out of trades, following more than one indicator, and following the markets closely.</p>
<p>If you want to stay updated on the latest options trades for United Rentals, <a href="https://benzinga.grsm.io/register174">Benzinga Pro</a> gives you real-time options trades alerts.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Analysts React To Intuitive Surgical Q3 Performance, Slash Price Targets</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/equities/23/10/35354393/analysts-react-to-intuitive-surgical-q3-performance-slash-price-targets</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/equities/23/10/35354393/analysts-react-to-intuitive-surgical-q3-performance-slash-price-targets</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:14:50 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Intuitive Surgical Inc&nbsp;</strong>(NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/ISRG#NASDAQ">ISRG</a>) shares fell by around 3%. Several analysts&nbsp;<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/ISRG/analyst-ratings" style="color:#4a6ee0; background:transparent; margin-top:0pt; margin-bottom:0pt" target="_blank">lowered estimates</a>&nbsp;post Q3 FY23 earnings.&nbsp;</p>

<p>ISRG reported quarterly earnings of $1.46 per share, which beat the analyst consensus estimate of $1.41, and sales of $1.74 billion, which missed the analyst&nbsp;<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35339565/intuitive-surgical-clocks-mixed-q3-earnings-stock-falls-after-hours" style="color:#4a6ee0; background:transparent; margin-top:0pt; margin-bottom:0pt" target="_blank">consensus estimate of $1.77 billion</a>.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The company revised its FY23 procedure volume outlook to 21%-22% (from 20%-22%), reflecting uncertainty around the duration of elevated procedure volumes with patients returning to health care, a continued slowing bariatric growth rates in the U.S. and macroeconomic challenges that could impact hospitals and patient spending.</p>

<p>Also, ISRG cut the gross margin outlook by 25bps at the midpoint to 68.0%-68.5% (vs. 68.0-69.0% previously) to reflect the timing of facilities completion, manufacturing efficiency improvements for new products and other complex projects and sees gross margin of = +70% over time in the medium term.</p>

<p><strong>RBC Capital Markets</strong>&nbsp;analyst&nbsp;<strong>Shagun Singh</strong>&nbsp;maintained the Outperform rating and a price target of $355.00.</p>

<p>The analyst estimates revenue of $7.09 billion (+14.1% y/y ex-fx) vs. consensus of $7.19 billion for FY23, including the assumed procedure volume growth of 21.5% y/y and systems shipped growth of 4.8% y/y.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Singh estimates EPS of $5.60 (+19.5% y/y), gross margin of 68.3% (-90bps y/y), and operating margin of 34.1% (-50bps y/y) for FY23.</p>

<p><strong>Piper Sandler</strong>&nbsp;analyst&nbsp;<strong>Adam C. Maeder</strong>&nbsp;reiterated the rating on the stock at Overweight and lowered the price target to $325 (from $385).&nbsp;</p>

<p>The analyst revised revenue and EPS estimates to $7,072.9 million (from $7,162.4 million) and $5.59 (from $5.58) for FY23 and $8,104.6 million (from $8,184.4 million) and $6.20 (from $6.43) for FY24.&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>Mizuho Securities</strong>&nbsp;analyst Anthony Petrone reaffirmed a Neutral rating and price target of $320.00.</p>

<p>The analyst lowered FY23 revenue and EPS estimates to $7.043 billion (from $7.103 billion) and $5.55 (from $5.45 earlier), reflecting a stable outlook for overall da Vinci procedures offset by a further slowdown in U.S. bariatrics and China capital placements.</p>

<p>The analyst writes that prevailing price levels will likely prove a floor through year-end as GLP-1/ China headwinds are further debated.</p>

<p><strong>William Blair&nbsp;</strong>analyst&nbsp;<strong>Brandon Vazquez</strong>&nbsp;maintained an Outperform rating.</p>

<p>The analyst sees several tailwinds to support double-digit sales and EPS growth in 2024, including continued uptake in U.S. general surgery, da Vinci SP adoption, Ion launch internationally, and potentially a next-gen multiport system.</p>

<p><strong>Raymond James</strong>&nbsp;analyst&nbsp;<strong>Jayson Bedford</strong>&nbsp;maintained an Outperform rating and lowered the price target to $310 from $368.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The analyst revised estimates for revenue and adjusted EPS to $7,062 million (from $7,127 million) and $5.60 (from $5.57) for FY23 and $7,887 million (from $8,141 million) and $6.22 (from $6.36) for FY24. This reflects higher leasing and slightly lower gross margins.&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>Price Action</strong>: ISRG shares are down 2.42% at $266.85 on the last check Friday.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>ManpowerGroup Bears The Brunt Of  Macro Woes Amid Weakness In Europe, Analyst Says Tough To Recommend This Name</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/23/10/35355916/manpowergroup-bears-the-brunt-of-macro-woes-amid-weakness-in-europe-analyst-says-to</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/23/10/35355916/manpowergroup-bears-the-brunt-of-macro-woes-amid-weakness-in-europe-analyst-says-to</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:14:43 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>BMO Capital Markets&nbsp;</strong>analyst Jeffrey M. Silber reiterates the Market Perform rating on&nbsp;<strong>ManpowerGroup&nbsp;</strong>(NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/MAN#NYSE">MAN</a>),&nbsp;<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/MAN/analyst-ratings" style="background-image:initial; background-position:initial; background-size:initial; background-repeat:initial; background-attachment:initial; background-origin:initial; background-clip:initial; margin-top:0pt; margin-bottom:0pt; color:#4a6ee0" target="_blank">lowering the price target to $79 from $88.</a></p>

<p>The company reported third-quarter FY23 results where revenues from services declined 2.6% year-on-year to $4.676 billion,&nbsp;<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/calendars/earnings" style="background-image:initial; background-position:initial; background-size:initial; background-repeat:initial; background-attachment:initial; background-origin:initial; background-clip:initial; margin-top:0pt; margin-bottom:0pt; color:#4a6ee0" target="_blank">missing the analyst consensus of $4.70 billion.</a>&nbsp;</p>

<p>Revenues fell 5%<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/earnings/23/10/35331963/why-workforce-solutions-company-manpowergroups-shares-are-trading-lower-today" style="background-image:initial; background-position:initial; background-size:initial; background-repeat:initial; background-attachment:initial; background-origin:initial; background-clip:initial; margin-top:0pt; margin-bottom:0pt; color:#4a6ee0" target="_blank">&nbsp;at constant currency.</a>&nbsp;</p>

<p>Geographically, Northern Europe was the largest miss compared to prior forecast, with other countries relatively in line on a CC basis, the analyst writes.</p>

<p>Management indicated further weakening through 3Q23 and some European Manpower brands weakening into 4Q23, though the analyst adds that some of this may have been baked-in given intra-quarter macro data.&nbsp;</p>

<p>In Q3, the analyst said Northern Europe&#39;s performance was most negative vs. guide alongside negative margins, given exposure to bench model countries.</p>

<p>Silber adds that MAN&#39;s valuation historically has been negatively impacted by its European exposure. Given greater recessionary fears in Europe, the analyst notes that it&#39;s tough to recommend this name.</p>

<p>Management noted it will not shy away from decisive actions to preserve margin though using a &quot;fine-point pen vs. a broad brush,&quot; the analyst adds.</p>

<p>Given the uncertainties, the analyst lowers the FY23 revenue estimate to $18.851 billion from the previous estimate of $19.160 billion.</p>

<p>Silber projects FY23 EPS of $5.78,&nbsp;<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/calendars/guidance" style="background-image:initial; background-position:initial; background-size:initial; background-repeat:initial; background-attachment:initial; background-origin:initial; background-clip:initial; margin-top:0pt; margin-bottom:0pt; color:#4a6ee0" target="_blank">lower than the previous estimate of $5.92.</a></p>

<p><strong>Price Action:</strong>&nbsp;MAN shares are trading higher by 1.45% to $70.51&nbsp;on the last check Friday.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Neutral on Kraft Heinz, Lowers Price Target to $34</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357104/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-kraft-heinz-lowers-price-target-to-34</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357104/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-kraft-heinz-lowers-price-target-to-34</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:12:38 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Michael Lavery   maintains Kraft Heinz (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/KHC#NASDAQ">KHC</a>) with a Neutral and lowers the price target from $41 to $34.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tractor Supply's Q3 Preview: Analyst Sees Tougher Comps, Macro Pressure &amp; More</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/23/10/35356329/tractor-supplys-q3-preview-analyst-sees-tougher-comps-macro-pressure-more</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/analyst-color/23/10/35356329/tractor-supplys-q3-preview-analyst-sees-tougher-comps-macro-pressure-more</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:12:33 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Telsey Advisory Group</strong>&nbsp;analyst Joseph Feldman reiterates the Outperform rating on&nbsp;<strong>Tractor Supply Company</strong>&nbsp;(NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TSCO#NASDAQ">TSCO</a>),&nbsp;<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/TSCO/analyst-ratings" style="background-image:initial; background-position:initial; background-size:initial; background-repeat:initial; background-attachment:initial; background-origin:initial; background-clip:initial; margin-top:0pt; margin-bottom:0pt; color:#4a6ee0" target="_blank">lowering the price target to $245 from $265.</a></p>

<p>Tractor Supply will report 3Q23 earnings on&nbsp;<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/calendars/earnings" style="background-image:initial; background-position:initial; background-size:initial; background-repeat:initial; background-attachment:initial; background-origin:initial; background-clip:initial; margin-top:0pt; margin-bottom:0pt; color:#4a6ee0" target="_blank">Thursday, October 26.</a></p>

<p>The analyst expects total sales growth of 7.0% to $3.5 billion, on a lower comp of 1.0% vs. 2.5% previously. Feldman revises&nbsp;<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/calendars/earnings" style="background-image:initial; background-position:initial; background-size:initial; background-repeat:initial; background-attachment:initial; background-origin:initial; background-clip:initial; margin-top:0pt; margin-bottom:0pt; color:#4a6ee0" target="_blank">3Q23 EPS estimate to $2.30 from $2.32.</a></p>

<p>Feldman&#39;s moderated sales forecast reflects Tractor Supply lapping difficult comparisons from the past three years fueled by heightened spending as a result of the pandemic and government stimulus&mdash;comps of 27%, 13%, and 6% in 3Q20, 3Q21, and 3Q22, respectively.</p>

<p>The analyst also sees slowing inflation weighing on average ticket, as the average monthly growth in the CPI fell to 3.5% in 3Q23 from 4.0% in 2Q23 and 8.3% in 3Q22.</p>

<p>The analyst also forecasts softening macro demand indicators&mdash;U.S. government industry retail sales were down 4.4% YoY in 3Q23, and the agricultural customer base is weaker, with corn prices and farmer incomes both down significantly.</p>

<p>Feldman projects inline&nbsp;<a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.benzinga.com/calendars/guidance" style="background-image:initial; background-position:initial; background-size:initial; background-repeat:initial; background-attachment:initial; background-origin:initial; background-clip:initial; margin-top:0pt; margin-bottom:0pt; color:#4a6ee0" target="_blank">gross margin expansion of 55 bps to 36.2%,&nbsp;</a>reflecting lower freight costs and benefits from strategic initiatives, partially offset by inflation and an unfavorable product mix shift toward C.U.E (consumable, usable and edible).&nbsp;</p>

<p>Given ongoing wage pressure and strategic investments, the analyst estimates roughly inline SG&amp;A ratio deleverage of ~10 bps to 26.4%.&nbsp;</p>

<p>The analyst projects an operating margin expansion of 38 bps to 9.7%.&nbsp;Given the unfavorable macro trends, the analyst lowers the 2024 EPS estimate to $11.05, down from $11.42.</p>

<p><strong>Price Action:</strong>&nbsp;TSCO shares are trading lower by 2.96% to $196.27 on the last check Friday.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>New Jersey Adult-Use Cannabis Licensing Advances As TerrAscend Faces Scrutiny</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35356854/new-jersey-adult-use-cannabis-licensing-advances-as-terrascend-faces-scrutiny</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35356854/new-jersey-adult-use-cannabis-licensing-advances-as-terrascend-faces-scrutiny</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:11:17 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The <strong>New Jersey Cannabis Regulatory Commission</strong> (NJ-CRC) recently made significant strides in the state&#39;s <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/cannabis">cannabis industry</a> by granting approvals for numerous licenses.</p>

<p><em>See Also:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35221499/new-jerseyites-dont-mind-smelling-weed-in-public-state-regulators-launch-cannabis-safety-campaig">New Jerseyites Don&#39;t Mind Smelling Weed In Public, State Regulators Launch Cannabis Safety Campaign</a></em></p>

<h3>New Jersey Approves 112 Adult-Use Cannabis Licenses, Expanding Market Activity</h3>

<p>The NJ-CRC approved a total of 112 adult-use cannabis licenses, comprising 40 conditional licenses, 52 conversions to annual licenses, and 20 annual license applications, as reported by <a href="https://headynj.com/nj-crc-approves-112-nj-adult-use-cannabis-licenses-reviews-terrascend-problems-again/">HEADYNJ</a>.</p>

<p>NJ-CRC executive director <strong>Jeff Brown</strong> noted that although the commission currently has numerous applications in inactive status due to businesses not responding to the its staff, there is growing activity in the New Jersey adult-use and medical cannabis market, with 60 dispensaries now operational.</p>

<p>Additionally, <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/topic/new-jersey-cannabis">New Jersey</a> is witnessing the emergence of adult-use-only cultivators and manufacturing cannabis, diversifying production within the market.</p>

<p><em>See Also:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35095410/nj-court-sets-precedent-employer-must-reimburse-worker-for-medical-marijuana-in-workers-comp-cas">NJ Court Sets Precedent: Employer Must Reimburse Worker For Medical Marijuana In Workers&#39; Comp Case</a></em></p>

<h3>On The Medical Cannabis Regulatory Side&hellip; NJ Regulators Addressing Compliance Concerns</h3>

<p><strong>TerrAscend Corp.</strong> (OTCQX:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TSNDF#OTCQX">TSNDF</a>) New Jersey&nbsp;recently violated medical cannabis rules said Brown. The company submitted a corrective action plan, but a subsequent violation occurred.</p>

<p>While the company <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/09/34441874/big-changes-coming-to-new-jerseys-cannabis-market-and-weed-giants-pay-fines">had previously faced multiple violations</a>, this latest breach was classified as a category 5 violation, potentially resulting in a maximum penalty of $10,000, noted Brown. However, the NJ-CRC decided not to recommend a fine in this instance.</p>

<p>&ldquo;Our goal here is compliance. Since that initial round of activity, they&rsquo;ve largely been compliant,&rdquo; Brown concluded.</p>

<p><em>Read Next:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/09/34982440/exclusive-why-terrascends-success-doesnt-rely-on-federal-cannabis-reform">EXCLUSIVE: Why TerrAscend&#39;s Success Doesn&#39;t Rely On Federal Cannabis Reform</a></em></p>

<p><em>Image by&nbsp;<a href="https://unsplash.com/es/@manisharaghunath?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Manisha Raghunath</a>&nbsp;On&nbsp;<a href="https://unsplash.com/es/fotos/horizonte-de-la-ciudad-a-traves-del-cuerpo-de-agua-durante-el-dia-ZaTM6pwKAuo?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Neutral on Truist Finl, Lowers Price Target to $31</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357090/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-truist-finl-lowers-price-target-to-31</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357090/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-truist-finl-lowers-price-target-to-31</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:10:50 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Stephen Scouten   maintains Truist Finl (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TFC#NYSE">TFC</a>) with a Neutral and lowers the price target from $32 to $31.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Overweight on Home BancShares, Lowers Price Target to $26</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357066/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-home-bancshares-lowers-price-target-to-26</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357066/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-home-bancshares-lowers-price-target-to-26</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:08:33 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Stephen Scouten   maintains Home BancShares (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/HOMB#NYSE">HOMB</a>) with a Overweight and lowers the price target from $27 to $26.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Neutral on Commerce Bancshares, Lowers Price Target to $51</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357043/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-commerce-bancshares-lowers-price-target-to-51</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35357043/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-commerce-bancshares-lowers-price-target-to-51</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:06:27 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Nathan Race   maintains Commerce Bancshares (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/CBSH#NASDAQ">CBSH</a>) with a Neutral and lowers the price target from $52 to $51.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cannabis Harvest Is Now: Industry Grapples Over Where And How To Get Enough Workers</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35357041/cannabis-harvest-is-now-industry-grapples-over-where-and-how-to-get-enough-workers</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35357041/cannabis-harvest-is-now-industry-grapples-over-where-and-how-to-get-enough-workers</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:06:11 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>As this year&#8217;s cannabis harvest season gets underway, competition for seasonal workers intensifies, reflecting broader economic challenges and shifts in the marijuana industry.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Layoffs And Labor Needs</h2>



<p><strong>Kate Robertson </strong>of MJBizDaily <a href="https://mjbizdaily.com/demand-for-seasonal-cannabis-harvest-workers-surges/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reports</a> that due to recent <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/01/30337184/cannabis-industrys-workforce-trimming-trend-continues-columbia-care-announces-dozens-of-layoffs" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">widespread layoffs</a>, many cultivators are now hiring temporary workers for the harvest.</p>



<p>The industry has experienced an unprecedented 2% drop in marijuana job numbers since early 2022, a first since states commenced the legalization of cannabis. This decrease, as reported by Denver&#8217;s Vangst, explains why marijuana cultivation <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/02/30896835/sndl-joins-tilray-canopy-and-curaleaf-in-force-reductions-layoffs-85-employees-at-olds-alberta-f" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">companies</a> are scrambling for temp workers for the impending fall harvest.</p>



<p><strong>Kara Bradford</strong>, CEO of Viridian Staffing, a Seattle-based cannabis recruitment firm, told MJBizDaily, "There have been a lot of layoffs over the past 18 months." She added, "So they're running slimmer crews and need that additional assistance because of harvest season."</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Competition for Seasonal Workers</h2>



<p><strong>Jacob Carlson</strong> of Boston&#8217;s EzHire Cannabis, pointed to the industry&#8217;s challenges, indicating that many companies "weren't able to actually build out a real cultivation team with full-time salaries or benefits." The demand for these temporary positions, however, conflicts with mainstream industries similarly seeking temporary workers, urged by similar macroeconomic pressures.</p>



<p>Adding to the complexity, cannabis harvest work, described as &#8220;more grueling than temporary retail jobs&#8221; by Carlson, often sees higher turnover. State-required background and criminal-record checks also create additional hurdles for growers hoping to hire a temporary cannabis workforce.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Financial Strains In A Maturing Market</h2>



<p>Yet, not all see the increased demand as a sign of distress. Vangst&#8217;s CEO, <strong>Karson Humiston</strong> interprets it as a signal of market maturity. "Companies have gotten better at projecting their labor needs given that the industry is continuing to mature," Humiston remarked to MJBizDaily.</p>



<p>Contrary to growers&#8217; expectations of temp workers being more affordable than full-time employees, Bradford said costs such as workers&#8217; compensation, unemployment insurance and training can accumulate. "It's an increase in demand, more need, but less funds to do so with," she said.</p>



<p>Large multistate operators with greater financial resources are often positioned more favorably, capable of offering competitive wages to attract seasonal workers. Conversely, smaller companies, constrained by budgetary limitations, grapple to keep pace.</p>



<p>To optimize hiring processes, experts advise cultivators to initiate recruitment efforts early.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Rise of Unions</h2>



<p>In this complex labor landscape, the emergence of cannabis workers <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/01/30552367/are-teamsters-just-warming-up-nearly-400-cannabis-workers-joined-the-union-since-jan-1st" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">unionizing</a> is another pivotal development. This trend underscores workers&#8217; <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/03/31477358/workers-at-two-more-cannabis-companies-unionize-with-teamsters-and-ufcw" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">quest</a> for enhanced working conditions and rights amid the industry&#8217;s rapid growth.</p>



<p><em>Photo from <a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Marijuana_bud_trimmer.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Wikimedia Commons</a></em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Watching Red Robin Gourmet Burgers; Traders Circulate Unconfirmed Rumor Newsletter Service Has Shorted The Stock</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/trading-ideas/23/10/35356997/watching-red-robin-gourmet-burgers-traders-circulate-unconfirmed-rumor-newsletter-service-has-short</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/trading-ideas/23/10/35356997/watching-red-robin-gourmet-burgers-traders-circulate-unconfirmed-rumor-newsletter-service-has-short</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:05:42 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Neutral on Westamerica Bancorp, Raises Price Target to $48</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356994/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-westamerica-bancorp-raises-price-target-to-48</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356994/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-westamerica-bancorp-raises-price-target-to-48</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:04:22 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Scott Siefers   maintains Westamerica Bancorp (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/WABC#NASDAQ">WABC</a>) with a Neutral and raises the price target from $46 to $48.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>David Beckham's Genius Business Decision That Ended Up Making Him $500M</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/general/sports/23/10/35355328/david-beckhams-genius-business-decision-that-ended-up-making-him-500m</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/general/sports/23/10/35355328/david-beckhams-genius-business-decision-that-ended-up-making-him-500m</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:02:41 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>David Beckham</strong> has reemerged in the headlines after <strong>Netflix Inc </strong>(NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/NFLX#NASDAQ">NFLX</a>) released a <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/entertainment/23/10/35203931/beckham-scores-for-netflix-kelce-for-amazon-messi-up-next-for-apple-sports-documentaries-hi" style="text-decoration-line:none">new documentary series</a> about Beckham and his wife, <strong>Victoria Beckham</strong>. Beckham was once one of the world&rsquo;s best soccer players, leading teams like Manchester United, <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/topic/soccer">Real Madrid and more.</a>&nbsp;</p>

<p><strong>Beckham&rsquo;s Business Brain: </strong>The sports world was shocked in 2007 when Beckham left Real Madrid, one of the premier teams in Europe, to join the LA Galaxy of MLS. At the time, the MLS was still very small compared to other soccer leagues around the world, so many thought it was questionable for Beckham to play in the MLS while he was still in his athletic prime.</p>

<p>But this is where Beckham&rsquo;s business savviness came into play. When Beckham joined the LA Galaxy, the MLS was only 10 years old. His contract came with an option to buy an expansion franchise for $25 million. Beckham retired in 2013 and exercised his option the following year, establishing Inter Miami.&nbsp;</p>

<p><em>Read Also: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/entertainment/23/10/35203931/beckham-scores-for-netflix-kelce-for-amazon-messi-up-next-for-apple-sports-documentaries-hi" style="text-decoration-line:none">Beckham Scores For Netflix, Kelce For Amazon, Messi Up Next For Apple: Sports Documentaries Hit Big For Streamers</a></em></p>

<p><strong>Andrew Petcash</strong>, the founder of Profluence Sports, outlined Beckham&rsquo;s incredible story in a <a href="https://twitter.com/AndrewPetcash/status/1557758420421382144?s=20" style="text-decoration-line:none">thread on X.com.</a> Petcash has grown a substantial following on X.com by making interesting threads related to athletes&#39; finances. He founded Profluence as a platform dedicated to aggregating insights, content and data about the future of sports and money.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Now, Inter Miami is worth more than $500 million and has one of the best players in the world, <strong>Lionel Messi</strong>, on its roster. The MLS has experienced dramatic growth in the United States&nbsp;since Beckham came in 2007, in part because he paved the way for other major soccer stars like Messi to come to the MLS.</p>

<p><em>Now Read: <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/general/entertainment/23/10/35322402/netflix-price-hike-shocks-us-uk-france-how-rival-streaming-giants-are-faring">Netflix Price Hike Shocks US, UK, France: How Rival Streaming Giants Are Faring</a></em></p>

<p><em>Photo:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/yahoo_pressebilder/" id="yui_3_16_0_1_1697828091548_42488" rel="author" title="Go to Yahoo Pressebilder's photostream">Yahoo Pressebilder</a>&nbsp;on Flickr</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Neutral on Discover Finl, Lowers Price Target to $96</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356912/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-discover-finl-lowers-price-target-to-96</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356912/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-discover-finl-lowers-price-target-to-96</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:01:45 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Kevin Barker   maintains Discover Finl (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/DFS#NYSE">DFS</a>) with a Neutral and lowers the price target from $100 to $96.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Analyst Expectations for Roper Techs's Future</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356886/analyst-expectations-for-roper-techss-future</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356886/analyst-expectations-for-roper-techss-future</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:53 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Roper Techs (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/ROP#NASDAQ">ROP</a>) has observed the following analyst ratings within the last quarter: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>These 8 analysts have an average price target of $558.25 versus the current price of Roper Techs at $484.74, implying  upside.</p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 8 analysts rated Roper Techs over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828449_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average has increased by 5.42% from the previous average price target of $529.57. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/ROP/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Roper Techs analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>Analyst Ratings: What Are They?</h1>
<p>Benzinga tracks 150 analyst firms and reports on their stock expectations. Analysts typically arrive at their conclusions by predicting how much money a company will make in the future, usually the upcoming five years, and how risky or predictable that company's revenue streams are.</p>
<p>Analysts attend company conference calls and meetings, research company financial statements, and communicate with insiders to publish their ratings on stocks. Analysts typically rate each stock once per quarter or whenever the company has a major update.</p>
<p>Some analysts also offer predictions for helpful metrics such as earnings, revenue, and growth estimates to provide further guidance as to what to do with certain tickers. It is important to keep in mind that while stock and sector analysts are specialists, they are also human and can only forecast their beliefs to traders.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CNN Reporter: GOP Rep Bergman Says He Is Running For Speaker</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35356882/cnn-reporter-gop-rep-bergman-says-he-is-running-for-speaker</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35356882/cnn-reporter-gop-rep-bergman-says-he-is-running-for-speaker</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:46 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<figure class="media"><oembed url="https://twitter.com/haleytalbotcnn/status/1715439962294833611"></oembed></figure>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Analyst Expectations for BILL Holdings's Future</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356881/analyst-expectations-for-bill-holdingss-future</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356881/analyst-expectations-for-bill-holdingss-future</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:46 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>BILL Holdings (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/BILL#NYSE">BILL</a>) has observed the following analyst ratings within the last quarter: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">9</td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">4</td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>According to 19 analyst offering 12-month price targets in the last 3 months, BILL Holdings has an average price target of $132.79 with a high of $200.00 and a low of $22.00. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 19 analysts rated BILL Holdings over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828442_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This average price target has increased by 23.18% over the past month.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/BILL/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on BILL Holdings analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>What Are Analyst Ratings?</h1>
<p>Analysts are specialists within banking and financial systems that typically report for specific stocks or within defined sectors. These people research company financial statements, sit in conference calls and meetings, and speak with relevant insiders to determine what are known as analyst ratings for stocks. Typically, analysts will rate each stock once a quarter. </p>
<p>Some analysts publish their predictions for metrics such as growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide additional guidance with their ratings. When using analyst ratings, it is important to keep in mind that stock and sector analysts are also human and are only offering their opinions to investors.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>$100 Invested In This Stock 20 Years Ago Would Be Worth $700 Today</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356877/100-invested-in-this-stock-20-years-ago-would-be-worth-700-today</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356877/100-invested-in-this-stock-20-years-ago-would-be-worth-700-today</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:40 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Honeywell Intl (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/HON#NASDAQ">HON</a>) has outperformed the market over the past 20 years by 2.56% on an annualized basis producing an average annual return of 9.77%. Currently, Honeywell Intl has a market capitalization of $121.55 billion. </p>
<p><strong>Buying $100 In HON:</strong> If an investor had bought $100 of HON stock 20 years ago, it would be worth <strong>$664.07</strong> today based on a price of $183.07 for HON at the time of writing.</p>
<h3>Honeywell Intl's Performance Over Last 20 Years</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828437_0.png" alt="comp_fig" /></p>

<p>Finally -- what's the point of all this? The key insight to take from this article is to note how much of a difference compounded returns can make in your cash growth over a period of time.</p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Analyst Ratings for Western Union</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356876/analyst-ratings-for-western-union</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356876/analyst-ratings-for-western-union</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:38 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past 3 months, 5 analysts have published their opinion on Western Union (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/WU#NYSE">WU</a>) stock. These analysts are typically employed by large Wall Street banks and tasked with understanding a company's business to predict how a stock will trade over the upcoming year.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>In the last 3 months, 5 analysts have offered 12-month price targets for Western Union. The company has an average price target of $13.2 with a high of $14.00 and a low of $12.50. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 5 analysts rated Western Union over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828434_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This average price target has increased by 11.11% over the past month.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/WU/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on Western Union analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>What Are Analyst Ratings?</h1>
<p>Ratings come from analysts, or specialists within banking and financial systems that report for specific stocks or defined sectors (typically once per quarter for each stock). Analysts usually derive their information from company conference calls and meetings, financial statements, and conversations with important insiders to reach their decisions.</p>
<p>Some analysts will also offer forecasts for metrics like growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide further guidance on stocks. Investors who use analyst ratings should note that this specialized advice comes from humans and may be subject to error.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Here's How Much $1000 Invested In Ross Stores 20 Years Ago Would Be Worth Today</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356874/heres-how-much-1000-invested-in-ross-stores-20-years-ago-would-be-worth-today</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356874/heres-how-much-1000-invested-in-ross-stores-20-years-ago-would-be-worth-today</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:35 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Ross Stores (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/ROST#NASDAQ">ROST</a>) has outperformed the market over the past 20 years by 4.39% on an annualized basis producing an average annual return of 11.6%. Currently, Ross Stores has a market capitalization of $39.45 billion. </p>
<p><strong>Buying $1000 In ROST:</strong> If an investor had bought $1000 of ROST stock 20 years ago, it would be worth <strong>$8,998.06</strong> today based on a price of $116.51 for ROST at the time of writing.</p>
<h3>Ross Stores's Performance Over Last 20 Years</h3>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828431_0.png" alt="comp_fig" /></p>

<p>Finally -- what's the point of all this? The key insight to take from this article is to note how much of a difference compounded returns can make in your cash growth over a period of time.</p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Litecoin Rises More Than 3% In 24 hours</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356873/litecoin-rises-more-than-3-in-24-hours</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356873/litecoin-rises-more-than-3-in-24-hours</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:36 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past 24 hours, <strong>Litecoin's</strong> (CRYPTO: <a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/ltc/usd">LTC</a>) price rose 3.51% to <strong>$63.39</strong>. This continues its positive trend over the past week where it has experienced a 3.0% gain, moving from $61.31 to its current price. As it stands right now, <strong>the coin's all-time high is $410.26</strong>. </p>
<p>The chart below compares the price movement and volatility for Litecoin over the past 24 hours (left) to its price movement over the past week (right). The gray bands are Bollinger Bands, measuring the volatility for both the daily and weekly price movements. The wider the bands are, or the larger the gray area is at any given moment, the larger the volatility.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828430_0.png" alt="price_chart" /></p>

<p>Litecoin's trading volume has climbed 25.0% over the past week, moving in tandem, directionally, with the overall circulating supply of the coin, which has increased 0.14%. This brings the circulating supply to 73.78 million, which makes up an estimated 87.84% of its max supply of 84.00 million. According to our data, the current market cap ranking for LTC is #17 at $4.67 billion.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828430_1.png" alt="supply_and_vol" /></p>

<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/api">Powered by CoinGecko API</a></p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Expert Ratings for TransDigm Gr</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356871/expert-ratings-for-transdigm-gr</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356871/expert-ratings-for-transdigm-gr</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:31 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Within the last quarter, TransDigm Gr (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/TDG#NYSE">TDG</a>) has observed the following analyst ratings: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">4</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">3</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>These 9 analysts have an average price target of $987.11 versus the current price of TransDigm Gr at $830.62, implying  upside.</p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 9 analysts rated TransDigm Gr over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828428_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This average price target has increased by 7.06% over the past month.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/TDG/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on TransDigm Gr analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>How Are Analyst Ratings Determined?</h1>
<p>Ratings come from analysts, or specialists within banking and financial systems that report for specific stocks or defined sectors (typically once per quarter for each stock). Analysts usually derive their information from company conference calls and meetings, financial statements, and conversations with important insiders to reach their decisions.</p>
<p>Some analysts publish their predictions for metrics such as growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide additional guidance with their ratings. When using analyst ratings, it is important to keep in mind that stock and sector analysts are also human and are only offering their opinions to investors.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>What 5 Analyst Ratings Have To Say About WNS (Hldgs)</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356870/what-5-analyst-ratings-have-to-say-about-wns-hldgs</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356870/what-5-analyst-ratings-have-to-say-about-wns-hldgs</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:24 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Analysts have provided the following ratings for WNS (Hldgs) (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/WNS#NYSE">WNS</a>) within the last quarter: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">4</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>In the last 3 months, 5 analysts have offered 12-month price targets for WNS (Hldgs). The company has an average price target of $83.0 with a high of $115.00 and a low of $65.00. </p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 5 analysts rated WNS (Hldgs) over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828421_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average represents a 16.44% decrease from the previous average price target of $99.33. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/WNS/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on WNS (Hldgs) analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<h1>Analyst Ratings: What Are They?</h1>
<p>Benzinga tracks 150 analyst firms and reports on their stock expectations. Analysts typically arrive at their conclusions by predicting how much money a company will make in the future, usually the upcoming five years, and how risky or predictable that company's revenue streams are.</p>
<p>Analysts attend company conference calls and meetings, research company financial statements, and communicate with insiders to publish their ratings on stocks. Analysts typically rate each stock once per quarter or whenever the company has a major update.</p>
<p>Some analysts also offer predictions for helpful metrics such as earnings, revenue, and growth estimates to provide further guidance as to what to do with certain tickers. It is important to keep in mind that while stock and sector analysts are specialists, they are also human and can only forecast their beliefs to traders.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Chainlink Rises More Than 3% In 24 hours</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356869/chainlink-rises-more-than-3-in-24-hours</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356869/chainlink-rises-more-than-3-in-24-hours</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:26 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past 24 hours, <strong>Chainlink's</strong> (CRYPTO: <a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/link/usd">LINK</a>) price rose 3.77% to <strong>$7.63</strong>. This continues its positive trend over the past week where it has experienced a 7.0% gain, moving from $7.17 to its current price. As it stands right now, <strong>the coin's all-time high is $52.70</strong>. </p>
<p>The chart below compares the price movement and volatility for Chainlink over the past 24 hours (left) to its price movement over the past week (right). The gray bands are Bollinger Bands, measuring the volatility for both the daily and weekly price movements. The wider the bands are, or the larger the gray area is at any given moment, the larger the volatility.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828420_0.png" alt="price_chart" /></p>

<p>Chainlink's trading volume has climbed 35.0% over the past week along with the circulating supply of the coin, which has increased 0.16%. This brings the circulating supply to 556.85 million, which makes up an estimated 55.68% of its max supply of 1.00 billion. According to our data, the current market cap ranking for LINK is #18 at $4.25 billion.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828420_1.png" alt="supply_and_vol" /></p>

<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/api">Powered by CoinGecko API</a></p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Where BankUnited Stands With Analysts</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356868/where-bankunited-stands-with-analysts</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/analyst-ratings/23/10/35356868/where-bankunited-stands-with-analysts</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:17 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Analysts have provided the following ratings for BankUnited (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/BKU#NYSE">BKU</a>) within the last quarter: </p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bullish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Indifferent</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Somewhat Bearish</strong></th>
<th align="right"><strong>Bearish</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Total Ratings</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">5</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Last 30D</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>1M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>2M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>3M Ago</strong></td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">2</td>
<td align="right">0</td>
<td align="right">1</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>These 6 analysts have an average price target of $26.67 versus the current price of BankUnited at $22.46, implying  upside.</p>
<p>Below is a summary of how these 6 analysts rated BankUnited over the past 3 months. The greater the number of bullish ratings, the more positive analysts are on the stock and the greater the number of bearish ratings, the more negative analysts are on the stock</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828413_0.png" alt="price target chart" /></p>

<p>This current average has increased by 1.29% from the previous average price target of $26.33. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/BKU/analyst-ratings?utm_source=Benzinga Insights"><strong>Stay up to date on BankUnited analyst ratings.</strong></a></p>
<p>If you are interested in following small-cap stock news and performance <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/news/small-cap">you can start by tracking it here</a>.</p>
<h1>Analyst Ratings: What Are They?</h1>
<p>Benzinga tracks 150 analyst firms and reports on their stock expectations. Analysts typically arrive at their conclusions by predicting how much money a company will make in the future, usually the upcoming five years, and how risky or predictable that company's revenue streams are.</p>
<p>Analysts attend company conference calls and meetings, research company financial statements, and communicate with insiders to publish their ratings on stocks. Analysts typically rate each stock once per quarter or whenever the company has a major update.</p>
<p>Some analysts publish their predictions for metrics such as growth estimates, earnings, and revenue to provide additional guidance with their ratings. When using analyst ratings, it is important to keep in mind that stock and sector analysts are also human and are only offering their opinions to investors.</p>
<p>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Polygon Up More Than 3% In 24 hours</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356865/polygon-up-more-than-3-in-24-hours</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/10/35356865/polygon-up-more-than-3-in-24-hours</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 15:00:15 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Polygon's</strong> (CRYPTO: <a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/quote/matic/usd">MATIC</a>) price has increased 3.92% over the past 24 hours to <strong>$0.54</strong>. Over the past week, MATIC has experienced an uptick of over 5.0%, moving from $0.51 to its current price.  As it stands right now, <strong>the coin's all-time high is $2.92</strong>. </p>
<p>The chart below compares the price movement and volatility for Polygon over the past 24 hours (left) to its price movement over the past week (right). The gray bands are Bollinger Bands, measuring the volatility for both the daily and weekly price movements. The wider the bands are, or the larger the gray area is at any given moment, the larger the volatility.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828409_0.png" alt="price_chart" /></p>

<p>Polygon's trading volume has climbed 59.0% over the past week, moving in tandem, directionally, with the overall circulating supply of the coin, which has increased 0.22%. This brings the circulating supply to 9.31 billion, which makes up an estimated 93.1% of its max supply of 10.00 billion. According to our data, the current market cap ranking for MATIC is #13 at $4.99 billion.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.benzinga.com/files/images/story/2023/1697828409_1.png" alt="supply_and_vol" /></p>

<p><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/api">Powered by CoinGecko API</a></p>
<p><em>This article was generated by Benzinga's automated content engine and reviewed by an editor.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Overweight on SL Green Realty, Lowers Price Target to $46</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356859/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-sl-green-realty-lowers-price-target-to-46</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356859/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-sl-green-realty-lowers-price-target-to-46</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:59:55 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Alexander Goldfarb   maintains SL Green Realty (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/SLG#NYSE">SLG</a>) with a Overweight and lowers the price target from $48 to $46.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Overweight on Liberty Energy, Raises Price Target to $26</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356850/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-liberty-energy-raises-price-target-to-26</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356850/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-liberty-energy-raises-price-target-to-26</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:58:24 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Luke Lemoine   maintains Liberty Energy (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/LBRT#NYSE">LBRT</a>) with a Overweight and raises the price target from $21 to $26.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hamas Released American-Israeli Hostages Judith And Natali Raanan</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35356848/hamas-released-american-israeli-hostages-judith-and-natali-raanan</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/economics/macro-economic-events/23/10/35356848/hamas-released-american-israeli-hostages-judith-and-natali-raanan</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:57:42 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-769433" title="https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-769433">https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/article-769433</a></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Overweight on Home Bancorp, Raises Price Target to $40</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356844/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-home-bancorp-raises-price-target-to-40</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356844/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-home-bancorp-raises-price-target-to-40</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:56:16 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Stephen Scouten   maintains Home Bancorp (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/HBCP#NASDAQ">HBCP</a>) with a Overweight and raises the price target from $38 to $40.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Neutral on Associated Banc, Lowers Price Target to $18</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356834/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-associated-banc-lowers-price-target-to-18</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356834/piper-sandler-maintains-neutral-on-associated-banc-lowers-price-target-to-18</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:54:21 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Scott Siefers   maintains Associated Banc (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/ASB#NYSE">ASB</a>) with a Neutral and lowers the price target from $18.5 to $18.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Cannabis + Creativity: New Documentary Explores Plant's Influence On Artists</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35355474/cannabis-creativity-new-documentary-explores-plants-influence-on-artists</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35355474/cannabis-creativity-new-documentary-explores-plants-influence-on-artists</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:53:00 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p>The link between <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/cannabis">cannabis</a> and creativity is explored in the recently released short documentary, <strong>&quot;Cannabis + Creativity.&quot;</strong> Featuring <strong>Sam Jones, Miyabe Shields, Treya Lam, Chef Ali, Kaya Nicole and Jasmine Mans,</strong> the film was executively produced by <strong>Etain</strong> and <strong>Dr. Nancy B. Austin.</strong> <strong>Elana Frankel,</strong> the director and producer, joined hands with <strong>Kassia Graham</strong> in the project, produced in partnership with <strong>Cabin Creek Films.</strong></p>

<p>Director Elana Frankel shared the essence of the documentary, stating, &quot;Can cannabis increase creativity? We set out to discover some answers in our documentary &#39;Cannabis + Creativity.&#39; We follow the creative process of six people from various backgrounds and professions to find out how the plant supports their lifestyle. They experiment, take risks, break rules and have fun, but in the end, they all use cannabis as a tool to express themselves.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Diving into the personal and professional lives of these six artists, the documentary showcases intimate interviews and reveals their unique creative processes, demonstrating the significant impact cannabis has on their artistic expression. The film&#39;s subjects range from composers and musicians to poets and designers, each underscoring the plant&#39;s vital role in their artistic endeavors.</p>

<p>Adding depth to the narrative, a skeptical grandmother is introduced, symbolizing the generational divide on cannabis use. Her reservations offer an engaging contrast to the ardent creators, stimulating a comprehensive discussion about cannabis&#39;s position in contemporary art and innovation.</p>

<p>Etain, the first and only&nbsp;women-founded medical cannabis dispensary in New York, is a prominent backer of the film. <strong>Jes Feuer,</strong> the marketing director at Etain, commented on the company&#39;s involvement.&nbsp;&quot;Etain is honored to support the making of the Cannabis + Creativity short documentary... We are so proud to support the team who created the film to highlight many of the women who share their stories of how cannabis not only has helped them heal and manage their day-to-day life, but also has given them meaning and powers them through their own creative endeavors.&quot;</p>

<p>The film invites viewers to a comprehensive insight into the crossroads of cannabis consumption and artistic innovation. Cannabis + Creativity is scheduled for screening as an official selection at the Catskill International Film Festival on Sunday, October 22nd.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Overweight on Intuitive Surgical, Lowers Price Target to $325</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356809/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-intuitive-surgical-lowers-price-target-to-325</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356809/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-intuitive-surgical-lowers-price-target-to-325</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:51:58 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Richard Repetto   maintains Intuitive Surgical (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/ISRG#NASDAQ">ISRG</a>) with a Overweight and lowers the price target from $385 to $325.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Small Pharma's Q2 2024 Financial Highlights Ahead Of Cybin Merger For Global DMT Business</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35354839/small-pharmas-q2-2024-financial-highlights-ahead-of-cybin-merger-for-global-dmt-business</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35354839/small-pharmas-q2-2024-financial-highlights-ahead-of-cybin-merger-for-global-dmt-business</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:49:11 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Small Pharma Inc. </strong>(OTCQB:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/DMTTF#OTCQB">DMTTF</a>), the short-acting psychedelics biotech <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/08/34074153/cybins-acquisition-of-small-pharma-will-elevate-dmt-therapeutics-for-depression-and-anxiety">about to be purchased</a> by Cybin Inc. (NYSE:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/CYBN#NYSE">CYBN</a>), published its interim&nbsp;financial results for Q2 ended August 31, 2023.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Numbers showed:</p>

<ul>
	<li>
	<p><strong>Cash</strong> of $5.6 (CA$7.68) million by August 31, vs. $13.5 million held by Feb. 28, 2023, a 58.6% six-month burn rate. And an <strong>almost 72% YoY decrease</strong> considering August 31, 2022&rsquo;s $19.8 million held in cash.</p>
	</li>
	<li>
	<p><strong>Six-month cash used in operating activities</strong> was $8.3 million vs. $8.98 million in the same comparable period in 2022.</p>
	</li>
	<li>
	<p><strong>Total non-operating expenses</strong> of $4.4 million and $8.6 million for three and six months of 2023, vs. $5.4 million and $9.7 million for the same periods in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
	</li>
	<li>
	<p>Of those, <strong>R&amp;D expenses</strong> totaled $1.67 million and $3.49 million for the three and six month periods ended August 31, 2023; as compared to $1.99 million and $3.5 million used in the same periods in 2022.</p>
	</li>
	<li>
	<p><strong>Net loss</strong> of $2.98 million and $7.1 million for the three and six months ended August 31, 2023; vs. $5.4 million and $9.7 million in the same comparable periods of 2022.</p>
	</li>
	<li>
	<p><strong>Deficit </strong>totaled almost $47 million by Aug. 31, 2023; vs. $39.9 million by Feb. 28 in a 17% six-month increase.</p>
	</li>
</ul>

<h3>Toward A Tight DMT Company</h3>

<p>This August 28, Small Pharma and Cybin <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/08/34074153/cybins-acquisition-of-small-pharma-will-elevate-dmt-therapeutics-for-depression-and-anxiety">entered into</a> a definitive arrangement&nbsp;for Cybin&rsquo;s acquisition of all Small Pharma&rsquo;s issued and outstanding securities in an all-share transaction.&nbsp;</p>

<p>On October 12, shareholders of both companies <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35245376/cybin-and-small-pharma-shareholders-green-light-acquisition-resolution-results-expected-dates">voted in favor</a> of the plan. On October 17, Small Pharma obtained a <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cannabis/23/10/35315422/moving-closer-to-cybin-acquisition-small-pharma-obtains-final-order-approving-arrangement">final approval order</a> from the BC Supreme Court which, together with satisfaction or waiver of other closing conditions, would enable the arrangement to close on or about Oct. 23, 2023.</p>

<p>Small Pharma&rsquo;s pipeline consists of short-duration psychedelic therapies targeting mental health conditions, most noticeably clinical-staged DMT-based assets SPL026 and SPL028.</p>

<p><strong>CEO George Tziras</strong> says Small Pharma has made &ldquo;exceptional progress&rdquo; over the past eight years and that the team is thrilled to enter &ldquo;the next stage of the company&rsquo;s evolution&rdquo; by combining its efforts and journey with Cybin.</p>

<p>The new combined company will be <strong>led by Cybin&rsquo;s CEO&nbsp;Doug Drysdale,</strong>&nbsp;&nbsp;while Tziras will join the board of directors.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Some of Small Pharma&rsquo;s senior management and staff will join the Cybin team toward executing the combined pipeline strategy, which points at building &ldquo;an international clinical-stage leader&rdquo; with two novel advanced and advancing psychedelic programs; and the industry&rsquo;s &ldquo;most advanced and well-protected&rdquo; DMT program with the largest&nbsp;combined dataset of research on native and modified DMT compounds.</p>

<p>Specific data on progress of the combined company&rsquo;s clinical programs and under-development is set to come following the arrangement&rsquo;s completion.</p>

<p><em>Photo: Benzinga edit with photo by&nbsp;PublicDomainPictures and&nbsp;janjf93 on&nbsp;Pixabay.</em></p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Overweight on Old Second Bancorp, Raises Price Target to $19</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356772/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-old-second-bancorp-raises-price-target-to-19</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356772/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-old-second-bancorp-raises-price-target-to-19</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:49:05 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Nathan Race   maintains Old Second Bancorp (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/OSBC#NASDAQ">OSBC</a>) with a Overweight and raises the price target from $17 to $19.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Piper Sandler Maintains Overweight on SolarEdge Technologies, Lowers Price Target to $110</title>
<link>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356749/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-solaredge-technologies-lowers-price-target-to-110</link>
<guid>https://www.benzinga.com/news/23/10/35356749/piper-sandler-maintains-overweight-on-solaredge-technologies-lowers-price-target-to-110</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 14:46:47 -0400</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[Piper Sandler  analyst Kashy Harrison   maintains SolarEdge Technologies (NASDAQ:<a class="ticker" href="https://www.benzinga.com/stock/SEDG#NASDAQ">SEDG</a>) with a Overweight and lowers the price target from $210 to $110.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>